{
	"description": "Find the longest word out of 5 given kanji",
	"deck": [
 { "question": "重白明入間", "answers": [ "明白", "めいはく", "あからさま" ], "comment": "明白 (めいはく, あからさま): obvious, clear, plain, evident, apparent, explicit, overt, plain, frank, candid, open, direct, straightforward, unabashed, blatant, flagrant"},
 { "question": "流王間安心", "answers": [ "安心", "あんしん", "あんじん" ], "comment": "安心 (あんしん, あんじん): relief, peace of mind, obtaining peace of mind through faith or ascetic practice"},
 { "question": "後給園安物", "answers": [ "安物", "やすもの" ], "comment": "安物 (やすもの): cheap article, poor quality article"},
 { "question": "花外数意給", "answers": [ "意外", "いがい" ], "comment": "意外 (いがい): unexpected, surprising"},
 { "question": "気花足交意", "answers": [ "意気", "いき" ], "comment": "意気 (いき): spirit, heart, disposition"},
 { "question": "念国気地意", "answers": [ "意気地", "いくじ", "いきじ" ], "comment": "意気地 (いくじ, いきじ): self-respect, self-confidence, guts, backbone, self-respect, self-confidence, guts, backbone"},
 { "question": "記見意歩時", "answers": [ "意見", "いけん" ], "comment": "意見 (いけん): opinion, view, comment"},
 { "question": "意記交命地", "answers": [ "意地", "いじ" ], "comment": "意地 (いじ): stubbornness, obstinacy, willpower, pride, disposition, nature, appetite, desire, greed"},
 { "question": "世園学空芸", "answers": [ "園芸学", "えんげいがく" ], "comment": "園芸学 (えんげいがく): study of horticulture"},
 { "question": "長作明園肉", "answers": [ "園長", "えんちょう" ], "comment": "園長 (えんちょう): head of a garden, kindergarten principal, nursery school principal, park director (botanical garden), zoo director (zoological garden), head of a plantation"},
 { "question": "国王給流色", "answers": [ "王国", "おうこく", "国王", "こくおう" ], "comment": "王国 (おうこく): kingdom, monarchy\n国王 (こくおう): king"},
 { "question": "手園作面王", "answers": [ "王手", "おうて" ], "comment": "王手 (おうて): check"},
 { "question": "器王安女本", "answers": [ "王女", "おうじょ", "おうにょ", "女王", "じょおう" ], "comment": "王女 (おうじょ, おうにょ): princess, princess\n女王 (じょおう): queen"},
 { "question": "王立術夜作", "answers": [ "王立", "おうりつ" ], "comment": "王立 (おうりつ): royal"},
 { "question": "真音年王楽", "answers": [ "音楽", "おんがく", "楽音", "がくおん" ], "comment": "音楽 (おんがく): music, musical movement\n楽音 (がくおん): musical note"},
 { "question": "声記理花音", "answers": [ "音声", "おんせい", "おんじょう", "声音", "せいおん", "こわね" ], "comment": "音声 (おんせい, おんじょう): voice, (the concept of) sound, voice, (the concept of) sound\n声音 (せいおん, こわね): vocal sound, tone of voice, vocal sound, tone of voice"},
 { "question": "格科立学流", "answers": [ "科学", "かがく", "学科", "がっか" ], "comment": "科学 (かがく): science\n学科 (がっか): study subject, course of study, department (university, etc.)"},
 { "question": "花流火文数", "answers": [ "火花", "ひばな", "花火", "はなび" ], "comment": "火花 (ひばな): spark\n花火 (はなび): fireworks"},
 { "question": "言器道火見", "answers": [ "火器", "かき" ], "comment": "火器 (かき): firearms, guns"},
 { "question": "術事音火春", "answers": [ "火事", "かじ" ], "comment": "火事 (かじ): fire, conflagration"},
 { "question": "力交用火見", "answers": [ "火力", "かりょく" ], "comment": "火力 (かりょく): heating power, steam power, firepower"},
 { "question": "命王花学元", "answers": [ "花王", "かおう" ], "comment": "花王 (かおう): peony, king of flowers"},
 { "question": "花白後数火", "answers": [ "火花", "ひばな", "花火", "はなび" ], "comment": "火花 (ひばな): spark\n花火 (はなび): fireworks"},
 { "question": "見雨念花命", "answers": [ "花見", "はなみ" ], "comment": "花見 (はなみ): cherry blossom viewing, flower viewing"},
 { "question": "立雨花道文", "answers": [ "花道", "はなみち", "かどう" ], "comment": "花道 (はなみち, かどう): passage through audience to stage, flower arrangement"},
 { "question": "会前色見楽", "answers": [ "会見", "かいけん" ], "comment": "会見 (かいけん): interview, audience"},
 { "question": "芸会白合親", "answers": [ "会合", "かいごう" ], "comment": "会合 (かいごう): meeting, assembly, association, conjunction"},
 { "question": "場生車番会", "answers": [ "会場", "かいじょう" ], "comment": "会場 (かいじょう): assembly hall, meeting place, venue, grounds"},
 { "question": "春科身食会", "answers": [ "会食", "かいしょく" ], "comment": "会食 (かいしょく): dining together, mess"},
 { "question": "時心肉園会", "answers": [ "会心", "かいしん" ], "comment": "会心 (かいしん): congeniality, satisfaction"},
 { "question": "作会芸空長", "answers": [ "会長", "かいちょう" ], "comment": "会長 (かいちょう): president (of a society), chairman"},
 { "question": "芸入外牛科", "answers": [ "外科", "げか" ], "comment": "外科 (げか): surgery, department of surgery (hospital, etc.)"},
 { "question": "目外会気念", "answers": [ "外気", "がいき" ], "comment": "外気 (がいき): open air"},
 { "question": "春外時見火", "answers": [ "外見", "がいけん", "そとみ" ], "comment": "外見 (がいけん, そとみ): outward appearance, outward appearance"},
 { "question": "徒交立芸外", "answers": [ "外交", "がいこう" ], "comment": "外交 (がいこう): diplomacy, selling (e.g. door-to-door), canvassing"},
 { "question": "白流実国外", "answers": [ "外国", "がいこく", "そとぐに", "国外", "こくがい" ], "comment": "外国 (がいこく, そとぐに): foreign country, foreign country\n国外 (こくがい): outside the country"},
 { "question": "人国外安音", "answers": [ "外国人", "がいこくじん" ], "comment": "外国人 (がいこくじん): foreigner, foreign citizen, foreign national, alien, non-Japanese"},
 { "question": "車念春声外", "answers": [ "外車", "がいしゃ", "車外", "しゃがい" ], "comment": "外車 (がいしゃ): foreign automobile\n車外 (しゃがい): outside a car"},
 { "question": "外真長給出", "answers": [ "外出", "がいしゅつ", "そとで" ], "comment": "外出 (がいしゅつ, そとで): outing, trip, going out, outing, trip, going out"},
 { "question": "食新真念外", "answers": [ "外食", "がいしょく" ], "comment": "外食 (がいしょく): eating out"},
 { "question": "記集人外進", "answers": [ "外人", "がいじん", "ほかびと", "ガイジン", "人外", "じんがい", "にんがい" ], "comment": "外人 (がいじん, ほかびと, ガイジン): foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider, foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider, foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider\n人外 (じんがい, にんがい): uninhabited area, acting inhumanly, inhuman person, nonhuman life (usu. sentient), uninhabited area, acting inhumanly, inhuman person, nonhuman life (usu. sentient)"},
 { "question": "給芸面代外", "answers": [ "外面", "がいめん", "そとづら", "げめん" ], "comment": "外面 (がいめん, そとづら, げめん): outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external, outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external, outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external"},
 { "question": "格世長安意", "answers": [ "格安", "かくやす" ], "comment": "格安 (かくやす): cheap, reasonable"},
 { "question": "言園命歩学", "answers": [ "学園", "がくえん" ], "comment": "学園 (がくえん): academy, campus"},
 { "question": "半声王学科", "answers": [ "科学", "かがく", "学科", "がっか" ], "comment": "科学 (かがく): science\n学科 (がっか): study subject, course of study, department (university, etc.)"},
 { "question": "物学時格会", "answers": [ "学会", "がっかい" ], "comment": "学会 (がっかい): scientific society, academic meeting, academic conference"},
 { "question": "学園芸合白", "answers": [ "園芸学", "えんげいがく" ], "comment": "園芸学 (えんげいがく): study of horticulture"},
 { "question": "配男学出術", "answers": [ "学術", "がくじゅつ" ], "comment": "学術 (がくじゅつ): science, learning, scholarship, arts and sciences, academic pursuits"},
 { "question": "学強草配生", "answers": [ "学生", "がくせい", "がくしょう", "がくそう" ], "comment": "学生 (がくせい, がくしょう, がくそう): student (esp. a university student), Heian-period student of government administration, Buddhist scholar, researcher at a Buddhist temple, person studying Buddhism, learning, scholarship, Heian-period student of government administration, Buddhist scholar, researcher at a Buddhist temple, person studying Buddhism, learning, scholarship"},
 { "question": "学記牛長春", "answers": [ "学長", "がくちょう" ], "comment": "学長 (がくちょう): university president"},
 { "question": "白学女徒所", "answers": [ "学徒", "がくと" ], "comment": "学徒 (がくと): student, follower, students and pupils"},
 { "question": "前和写内学", "answers": [ "学内", "がくない" ], "comment": "学内 (がくない): within the school"},
 { "question": "器草面学年", "answers": [ "学年", "がくねん" ], "comment": "学年 (がくねん): academic year, school year, year in school, grade in school"},
 { "question": "身物学力格", "answers": [ "学力", "がくりょく", "力学", "りきがく" ], "comment": "学力 (がくりょく): scholarly ability, scholarship, knowledge, literary ability\n力学 (りきがく): mechanics, dynamics"},
 { "question": "新出写園楽", "answers": [ "楽園", "らくえん" ], "comment": "楽園 (らくえん): pleasure garden, paradise"},
 { "question": "作元見楽器", "answers": [ "楽器", "がっき", "器楽", "きがく" ], "comment": "楽器 (がっき): musical instrument\n器楽 (きがく): instrumental music"},
 { "question": "歩間念音食", "answers": [ "間食", "かんしょく", "食間", "しょっかん" ], "comment": "間食 (かんしょく): eating between meals, snacking\n食間 (しょっかん): between meals"},
 { "question": "間強中見理", "answers": [ "間中", "あいだじゅう", "中間", "ちゅうかん", "ちゅうげん" ], "comment": "間中 (あいだじゅう): during\n中間 (ちゅうかん, ちゅうげん): middle, midway, interim, samurai's attendant, footman"},
 { "question": "所物親器数", "answers": [ "器物", "きぶつ", "うつわもの" ], "comment": "器物 (きぶつ, うつわもの): container, receptacle, utensil, implement, furniture, calibre, talent, ability, personal property, container, receptacle, utensil, implement, furniture, calibre, talent, ability, personal property"},
 { "question": "写器雨肉用", "answers": [ "器用", "きよう", "用器", "ようき" ], "comment": "器用 (きよう): nimble-fingered, dexterous, dextrous, skillful (with the fingers), skilful, handy, clever, shrewd, ingenious\n用器 (ようき): tool, instrument"},
 { "question": "気徒楽白写", "answers": [ "気楽", "きらく" ], "comment": "気楽 (きらく): carefree, comfortable, at ease, easygoing, happy-go-lucky"},
 { "question": "科気心器先", "answers": [ "気心", "きごころ", "心気", "しんき" ], "comment": "気心 (きごころ): temper, disposition\n心気 (しんき): mentality, mood, sentiment, feelings, fretfulness, tedium"},
 { "question": "実格前芸気", "answers": [ "気前", "きまえ" ], "comment": "気前 (きまえ): generosity"},
 { "question": "体科会牛気", "answers": [ "気体", "きたい" ], "comment": "気体 (きたい): vapour, vapor, gas"},
 { "question": "足進気器配", "answers": [ "気配", "けはい", "きはい" ], "comment": "気配 (けはい, きはい): indication, sign, hint, presence, trend, quotation (esp. stock market), indication, sign, hint, presence, trend, quotation (esp. stock market)"},
 { "question": "肉花分用気", "answers": [ "気分", "きぶん" ], "comment": "気分 (きぶん): feeling, mood"},
 { "question": "気芸力食王", "answers": [ "気力", "きりょく" ], "comment": "気力 (きりょく): willpower, energy, vitality"},
 { "question": "発男元事記", "answers": [ "記事", "きじ" ], "comment": "記事 (きじ): article, news story, report, account"},
 { "question": "心記文給入", "answers": [ "記入", "きにゅう" ], "comment": "記入 (きにゅう): entry, filling in of forms"},
 { "question": "念歩真記雨", "answers": [ "記念", "きねん" ], "comment": "記念 (きねん): commemoration, celebration, honoring the memory of something, turning something into a memento, memory"},
 { "question": "念音新記日", "answers": [ "記念日", "きねんび" ], "comment": "記念日 (きねんび): holiday, anniversary, memorial day"},
 { "question": "食園王車給", "answers": [ "給食", "きゅうしょく" ], "comment": "給食 (きゅうしょく): provision of lunch (e.g. at office, school, etc.), providing a meal, lunch service"},
 { "question": "給格術実水", "answers": [ "給水", "きゅうすい" ], "comment": "給水 (きゅうすい): water supply"},
 { "question": "世行肉牛番", "answers": [ "牛肉", "ぎゅうにく", "肉牛", "にくぎゅう" ], "comment": "牛肉 (ぎゅうにく): beef\n肉牛 (にくぎゅう): beef cattle"},
 { "question": "手気半食強", "answers": [ "強気", "つよき", "ごうぎ", "ごうき" ], "comment": "強気 (つよき, ごうぎ, ごうき): confident, assured, self-assured, firm, strong, cocksure, bullish (e.g. market), great, grand, obstinate, stubborn, great, grand, obstinate, stubborn"},
 { "question": "王強番行元", "answers": [ "強行", "きょうこう" ], "comment": "強行 (きょうこう): forcing, enforcement, forced, enforced"},
 { "question": "写大集強元", "answers": [ "強大", "きょうだい" ], "comment": "強大 (きょうだい): mighty, powerful"},
 { "question": "色所強器風", "answers": [ "強風", "きょうふう" ], "comment": "強風 (きょうふう): strong wind, high wind, moderate gale"},
 { "question": "配力強用女", "answers": [ "強力", "きょうりょく", "ごうりき" ], "comment": "強力 (きょうりょく, ごうりき): powerful, strong, herculean strength, mountain carrier-guide"},
 { "question": "地空男王記", "answers": [ "空地", "あきち", "くうち" ], "comment": "空地 (あきち, くうち): vacant land, vacant land"},
 { "question": "間実命空徒", "answers": [ "実空間", "じつくうかん" ], "comment": "実空間 (じつくうかん): position space (quantum mechanics), real space"},
 { "question": "気空草牛出", "answers": [ "空気", "くうき" ], "comment": "空気 (くうき): air, atmosphere, mood, situation, someone with no presence, someone who doesn't stand out at all"},
 { "question": "和交空車男", "answers": [ "空車", "くうしゃ", "からぐるま", "あきぐるま" ], "comment": "空車 (くうしゃ, からぐるま, あきぐるま): empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available, empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available, empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available"},
 { "question": "手空意園日", "answers": [ "空手", "からて" ], "comment": "空手 (からて): karate, empty handed"},
 { "question": "心芸肉前空", "answers": [ "空前", "くうぜん" ], "comment": "空前 (くうぜん): unprecedented, record-breaking"},
 { "question": "場中空交先", "answers": [ "空中", "くうちゅう", "中空", "ちゅうくう", "なかぞら" ], "comment": "空中 (くうちゅう): sky, air\n中空 (ちゅうくう, なかぞら): hollow, emptiness, mid-air, the air, hollow, emptiness, mid-air, the air"},
 { "question": "空進念白春", "answers": [ "空白", "くうはく" ], "comment": "空白 (くうはく): blank space, vacuum, space, null (NUL)"},
 { "question": "術地時芸言", "answers": [ "芸術", "げいじゅつ" ], "comment": "芸術 (げいじゅつ): (fine) art, the arts"},
 { "question": "人配芸夜草", "answers": [ "芸人", "げいにん" ], "comment": "芸人 (げいにん): player, performer, actor"},
 { "question": "名先長芸内", "answers": [ "芸名", "げいめい" ], "comment": "芸名 (げいめい): stage name"},
 { "question": "真間徒月和", "answers": [ "月間", "げっかん" ], "comment": "月間 (げっかん): month-long period, (during) month"},
 { "question": "草月力器給", "answers": [ "月給", "げっきゅう" ], "comment": "月給 (げっきゅう): monthly salary"},
 { "question": "見時音草月", "answers": [ "月見草", "つきみそう" ], "comment": "月見草 (つきみそう): evening primrose (esp. the fourwing evening primrose, Oenothera tetraptera)"},
 { "question": "合春食数月", "answers": [ "月食", "げっしょく" ], "comment": "月食 (げっしょく): lunar eclipse"},
 { "question": "月年流心日", "answers": [ "年月日", "ねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "年月日 (ねんがっぴ): date"},
 { "question": "月面所念合", "answers": [ "月面", "げつめん" ], "comment": "月面 (げつめん): moon's surface"},
 { "question": "夜草月時芸", "answers": [ "月夜", "つきよ" ], "comment": "月夜 (つきよ): moonlit night"},
 { "question": "王見学肉身", "answers": [ "見学", "けんがく" ], "comment": "見学 (けんがく): inspection, study by observation, field trip"},
 { "question": "事流草見男", "answers": [ "見事", "みごと" ], "comment": "見事 (みごと): splendid, magnificent, beautiful, admirable, praiseworthy act, feat, commendable deed, utter (esp. defeat), total, complete"},
 { "question": "牛見記地時", "answers": [ "見地", "けんち" ], "comment": "見地 (けんち): point of view"},
 { "question": "時見念物重", "answers": [ "見物", "けんぶつ", "みもの", "物見", "ものみ" ], "comment": "見物 (けんぶつ, みもの): sightseeing, watching, viewing, sightseer, watcher, spectator, sight, attraction, spectacle, something worth seeing\n物見 (ものみ): sightseeing, scout, patrol, watchtower, lookout"},
 { "question": "園物人雨見", "answers": [ "見物人", "けんぶつにん" ], "comment": "見物人 (けんぶつにん): spectator, sightseer, onlookers"},
 { "question": "見空男肉本", "answers": [ "見本", "みほん" ], "comment": "見本 (みほん): sample, specimen, pattern, model, example"},
 { "question": "園気元番草", "answers": [ "元気", "げんき" ], "comment": "元気 (げんき): lively, full of spirit, energetic, vigorous, vital, spirited, healthy, well, fit, in good health"},
 { "question": "流牛日進元", "answers": [ "元日", "がんじつ", "がんにち" ], "comment": "元日 (がんじつ, がんにち): New Year's Day, New Year's Day"},
 { "question": "雨世元体年", "answers": [ "元年", "がんねん" ], "comment": "元年 (がんねん): first year (of a specific reign)"},
 { "question": "新元空本徒", "answers": [ "元本", "がんぽん", "げんぽん", "本元", "ほんもと" ], "comment": "元本 (がんぽん, げんぽん): principal (invest.), capital, principal (invest.), capital\n本元 (ほんもと): origin, main branch of family"},
 { "question": "大紙真後見", "answers": [ "後見", "こうけん" ], "comment": "後見 (こうけん): guardianship, guardian, (theatrical) assistant, prompter"},
 { "question": "手後白和春", "answers": [ "後手", "ごて" ], "comment": "後手 (ごて): losing initiative, being forestalled, second move (in go or shogi), moving second, person with the second move, rear guard"},
 { "question": "空後徒意世", "answers": [ "後世", "こうせい", "ごせ" ], "comment": "後世 (こうせい, ごせ): posterity, future life, life to come, the next world, afterlife, life after death"},
 { "question": "日後紙園会", "answers": [ "後日", "ごじつ", "ごにち" ], "comment": "後日 (ごじつ, ごにち): in the future, another day, later, in the future, another day, later"},
 { "question": "間発名後肉", "answers": [ "後発", "こうはつ" ], "comment": "後発 (こうはつ): starting late"},
 { "question": "後色真芸半", "answers": [ "後半", "こうはん" ], "comment": "後半 (こうはん): second half, latter half"},
 { "question": "食番交心半", "answers": [ "交番", "こうばん" ], "comment": "交番 (こうばん): police box, small neighborhood police station, alternation, alternating (e.g. current)"},
 { "question": "交前楽発流", "answers": [ "交流", "こうりゅう" ], "comment": "交流 (こうりゅう): (cultural) exchange, interchange, interaction, (inter-) mingling, (social, etc.) networking, intercourse, alternating current, AC"},
 { "question": "見楽行命格", "answers": [ "行楽", "こうらく" ], "comment": "行楽 (こうらく): outing, picnic, excursion, pleasure trip"},
 { "question": "行念風事声", "answers": [ "行事", "ぎょうじ" ], "comment": "行事 (ぎょうじ): event, function"},
 { "question": "牛行進術音", "answers": [ "行進", "こうしん", "進行", "しんこう" ], "comment": "行進 (こうしん): march, parade\n進行 (しんこう): moving forward (e.g. vehicle), onward movement, advance (work, procedure, etc), advancement, progress, progress (of a disease), disease progression, progression (harmonic, melodic)"},
 { "question": "言意王念合", "answers": [ "合意", "ごうい" ], "comment": "合意 (ごうい): agreement, consent, mutual understanding, accord"},
 { "question": "真長合進格", "answers": [ "合格", "ごうかく" ], "comment": "合格 (ごうかく): success, passing (e.g. exam), eligibility"},
 { "question": "間身春給合", "answers": [ "間合", "まあい", "合間", "あいま" ], "comment": "間合 (まあい): interval, distance, break, pause, suitable time, appropriate opportunity, distance between opponents (kendo)\n合間 (あいま): interval, break, pause, spare moment"},
 { "question": "作王合写足", "answers": [ "合作", "がっさく" ], "comment": "合作 (がっさく): collaboration, joint work"},
 { "question": "理合車時長", "answers": [ "合理", "ごうり" ], "comment": "合理 (ごうり): rational"},
 { "question": "文花合力世", "answers": [ "合力", "ごうりょく", "ごうりき", "こうりょく" ], "comment": "合力 (ごうりょく, ごうりき, こうりょく): resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving, resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving, resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving"},
 { "question": "作国春王肉", "answers": [ "王国", "おうこく", "国王", "こくおう" ], "comment": "王国 (おうこく): kingdom, monarchy\n国王 (こくおう): king"},
 { "question": "親新音国会", "answers": [ "国会", "こっかい" ], "comment": "国会 (こっかい): National Diet, parliament, congress"},
 { "question": "写器外国配", "answers": [ "外国", "がいこく", "そとぐに", "国外", "こくがい" ], "comment": "外国 (がいこく, そとぐに): foreign country, foreign country\n国外 (こくがい): outside the country"},
 { "question": "交間国牛念", "answers": [ "国交", "こっこう" ], "comment": "国交 (こっこう): diplomatic relations"},
 { "question": "大春国夜世", "answers": [ "国大", "こくだい", "大国", "たいこく" ], "comment": "国大 (こくだい): national university\n大国 (たいこく): large country, major powers"},
 { "question": "写女道代国", "answers": [ "国道", "こくどう" ], "comment": "国道 (こくどう): national highway"},
 { "question": "国内白代音", "answers": [ "国内", "こくない", "こくだい", "くぬち", "内国", "ないこく" ], "comment": "国内 (こくない, こくだい, くぬち): internal, domestic, internal, domestic, internal, domestic\n内国 (ないこく): home country"},
 { "question": "理春肉国名", "answers": [ "国名", "こくめい" ], "comment": "国名 (こくめい): country name"},
 { "question": "発時立国歩", "answers": [ "国立", "こくりつ", "立国", "りっこく" ], "comment": "国立 (こくりつ): national\n立国 (りっこく): founding of a nation"},
 { "question": "園分風紙作", "answers": [ "作風", "さくふう" ], "comment": "作風 (さくふう): literary style"},
 { "question": "作番牛物楽", "answers": [ "作物", "さくぶつ", "さくもつ" ], "comment": "作物 (さくぶつ, さくもつ): literary work, produce (e.g. agricultural), crops"},
 { "question": "道記数文作", "answers": [ "作文", "さくぶん", "さくもん" ], "comment": "作文 (さくぶん, さくもん): writing (an essay, prose, etc.), composition, formal writing with little real meaning, writing (poetry), composing"},
 { "question": "術用見作音", "answers": [ "作用", "さよう" ], "comment": "作用 (さよう): action, operation, effect, function"},
 { "question": "面紙作番牛", "answers": [ "紙面", "しめん" ], "comment": "紙面 (しめん): space (page)"},
 { "question": "念交後事新", "answers": [ "後事", "こうじ", "事後", "じご" ], "comment": "後事 (こうじ): future affairs, affairs after one's death\n事後 (じご): after-, post-, ex-, after the fact, ex post"},
 { "question": "会実事肉水", "answers": [ "事実", "じじつ", "実事", "じつごと", "じつじ" ], "comment": "事実 (じじつ): fact, truth, reality\n実事 (じつごと, じつじ): fact, (a) truth, realistic portrayal of an ordinary event (by a wise man), fact, (a) truth, realistic portrayal of an ordinary event (by a wise man)"},
 { "question": "重前事安念", "answers": [ "事前", "じぜん" ], "comment": "事前 (じぜん): prior, beforehand, in advance, before the fact, ex ante"},
 { "question": "時雨外芸火", "answers": [ "時雨", "しぐれ", "じう" ], "comment": "時雨 (しぐれ, じう): drizzle, shower in late autumn (fall) or early winter, seasonable rain, drizzle, shower in late autumn (fall) or early winter, seasonable rain"},
 { "question": "間時長見親", "answers": [ "長時間", "ちょうじかん" ], "comment": "長時間 (ちょうじかん): long period of time, long playing"},
 { "question": "合術時給身", "answers": [ "時給", "じきゅう" ], "comment": "時給 (じきゅう): hourly pay, hourly wage"},
 { "question": "園外代時元", "answers": [ "時代", "じだい" ], "comment": "時代 (じだい): period, epoch, era, age, the times, those days, oldness, ancientness, antiquity, antique, period piece"},
 { "question": "時実行集立", "answers": [ "実行時", "じっこうじ" ], "comment": "実行時 (じっこうじ): execution-time, run time, object time"},
 { "question": "数長徒実前", "answers": [ "実数", "じっすう" ], "comment": "実数 (じっすう): real number"},
 { "question": "交体明実出", "answers": [ "実体", "じったい" ], "comment": "実体 (じったい): substance, entity, object"},
 { "question": "給春安地実", "answers": [ "実地", "じっち" ], "comment": "実地 (じっち): practice, the actual site"},
 { "question": "世物場実念", "answers": [ "実物", "じつぶつ", "みもの" ], "comment": "実物 (じつぶつ, みもの): real thing, original, actual, ornamental plant used primarily for the visual effect of its fruit"},
 { "question": "面集風実名", "answers": [ "実名", "じつめい", "名実", "めいじつ" ], "comment": "実名 (じつめい): real name\n名実 (めいじつ): in name and in reality, nominally and virtually, form and contents"},
 { "question": "番実配雨用", "answers": [ "実用", "じつよう" ], "comment": "実用 (じつよう): practical use, utility"},
 { "question": "歩力言実長", "answers": [ "実力", "じつりょく" ], "comment": "実力 (じつりょく): (real) ability, true strength, merit, efficiency, competency, arms, force"},
 { "question": "写明科園真", "answers": [ "写真", "しゃしん" ], "comment": "写真 (しゃしん): photograph, photo, picture, snapshot, snap, movie"},
 { "question": "親安入生写", "answers": [ "写生", "しゃせい" ], "comment": "写生 (しゃせい): sketching, drawing from nature, portrayal, description"},
 { "question": "体命車写元", "answers": [ "車体", "しゃたい" ], "comment": "車体 (しゃたい): body (of car), frame"},
 { "question": "車道園徒強", "answers": [ "車道", "しゃどう" ], "comment": "車道 (しゃどう): roadway"},
 { "question": "内行会車術", "answers": [ "車内", "しゃない" ], "comment": "車内 (しゃない): inside a train, car, etc."},
 { "question": "面集手給間", "answers": [ "手間", "てま" ], "comment": "手間 (てま): time, labour, labor"},
 { "question": "用記世科手", "answers": [ "手記", "しゅき" ], "comment": "手記 (しゅき): note, memorandum"},
 { "question": "世元器手作", "answers": [ "元手", "もとで", "手元", "てもと" ], "comment": "元手 (もとで): funds, capital, stock\n手元 (てもと): at hand, on hand, nearby, close at hand, way of moving one's arms, skill, money at hand, pocket money, grip, handle"},
 { "question": "進楽手場紙", "answers": [ "手紙", "てがみ" ], "comment": "手紙 (てがみ): letter"},
 { "question": "声術世手真", "answers": [ "手術", "しゅじゅつ" ], "comment": "手術 (しゅじゅつ): (surgical) operation, procedure"},
 { "question": "明気数手出", "answers": [ "手数", "てすう", "てかず" ], "comment": "手数 (てすう, てかず): trouble, bother, number of moves (in go, shogi, etc.), number of punches (in boxing), trouble, bother, number of moves (in go, shogi, etc.), number of punches (in boxing)"},
 { "question": "手道牛前親", "answers": [ "手前", "てまえ", "てめえ" ], "comment": "手前 (てまえ, てめえ): before, this side, one's standpoint, one's appearance, we, you, you (used by young males), oneself"},
 { "question": "足肉夜手物", "answers": [ "手足", "てあし" ], "comment": "手足 (てあし): one's hands and feet, limbs"},
 { "question": "理手配牛用", "answers": [ "手配", "てはい" ], "comment": "手配 (てはい): arrangement, preparations, search (by police)"},
 { "question": "明手風本立", "answers": [ "手本", "てほん", "本手", "ほんて" ], "comment": "手本 (てほん): copybook, model, pattern\n本手 (ほんて): one's true ability, the right way, professional"},
 { "question": "会集外世術", "answers": [ "会集", "かいしゅう", "集会", "しゅうかい" ], "comment": "会集 (かいしゅう): audience, assembly, meeting\n集会 (しゅうかい): meeting, assembly, gathering, congregation, convention, rally"},
 { "question": "先集名強合", "answers": [ "集合", "しゅうごう" ], "comment": "集合 (しゅうごう): gathering, assembly, meeting, set"},
 { "question": "出科集中念", "answers": [ "集中", "しゅうちゅう" ], "comment": "集中 (しゅうちゅう): concentration, convergence, centralization, integration, gathering together"},
 { "question": "数風重長心", "answers": [ "重心", "じゅうしん" ], "comment": "重心 (じゅうしん): centre of gravity (center), centroid, barycenter, (one's) balance"},
 { "question": "重大歩見写", "answers": [ "重大", "じゅうだい" ], "comment": "重大 (じゅうだい): serious, important, significant, grave, weighty"},
 { "question": "格集力先重", "answers": [ "重力", "じゅうりょく" ], "comment": "重力 (じゅうりょく): gravity, gravitation, gravitational pull"},
 { "question": "給夜火出意", "answers": [ "出火", "しゅっか" ], "comment": "出火 (しゅっか): outbreak of fire"},
 { "question": "術出場声月", "answers": [ "出場", "しゅつじょう", "でば" ], "comment": "出場 (しゅつじょう, でば): (stage) appearance, performance, participation (e.g. in a tournament), one's time (e.g. to go on stage), one's turn, source, origin, place of production"},
 { "question": "面配出身写", "answers": [ "出身", "しゅっしん" ], "comment": "出身 (しゅっしん): person's origin (e.g. city, country, parentage, school)"},
 { "question": "集草世出間", "answers": [ "出世間", "しゅっせけん" ], "comment": "出世間 (しゅっせけん): monastic life"},
 { "question": "集前間和出", "answers": [ "出前", "でまえ", "前出", "ぜんしゅつ" ], "comment": "出前 (でまえ): catering, meal delivery service\n前出 (ぜんしゅつ): aforementioned, discussed above, former, previous"},
 { "question": "出内足間器", "answers": [ "出足", "であし" ], "comment": "出足 (であし): turnout (of people), start (e.g. race, campaign, term of office), constant forward movement, initial charge, dash"},
 { "question": "入雨明出親", "answers": [ "出入", "しゅつにゅう" ], "comment": "出入 (しゅつにゅう): in and out, income and expenses, free associations, run of the house"},
 { "question": "牛出用発記", "answers": [ "出発", "しゅっぱつ", "発出", "はっしゅつ" ], "comment": "出発 (しゅっぱつ): departure\n発出 (はっしゅつ): issue, sending out"},
 { "question": "出中草番王", "answers": [ "出番", "でばん" ], "comment": "出番 (でばん): one's turn"},
 { "question": "面安力王出", "answers": [ "出力", "しゅつりょく" ], "comment": "出力 (しゅつりょく): output (electrical, signal, etc.)"},
 { "question": "先春道交強", "answers": [ "春先", "はるさき" ], "comment": "春先 (はるさき): beginning of spring"},
 { "question": "春足分歩草", "answers": [ "春分", "しゅんぶん" ], "comment": "春分 (しゅんぶん): vernal equinox, spring equinox"},
 { "question": "見前新給所", "answers": [ "所見", "しょけん", "見所", "みどころ", "けんじょ", "けんしょ" ], "comment": "所見 (しょけん): view, opinion, finding, findings\n見所 (みどころ, けんじょ, けんしょ): point worthy of note, highlight (e.g. in a film), thing to note, good prospects for the future, promise, audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh), audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh)"},
 { "question": "白長世所火", "answers": [ "所長", "しょちょう", "長所", "ちょうしょ" ], "comment": "所長 (しょちょう): chief, head (of an office, of a laboratory)\n長所 (ちょうしょ): strong point, merit, virtue, advantage"},
 { "question": "写王女園歩", "answers": [ "王女", "おうじょ", "おうにょ", "女王", "じょおう" ], "comment": "王女 (おうじょ, おうにょ): princess, princess\n女王 (じょおう): queen"},
 { "question": "女文流術外", "answers": [ "女流", "じょりゅう" ], "comment": "女流 (じょりゅう): woman (writer, artist, aviator, etc.)"},
 { "question": "長場合花明", "answers": [ "場合", "ばあい" ], "comment": "場合 (ばあい): case, situation"},
 { "question": "命術場所念", "answers": [ "場所", "ばしょ", "所場", "しょば", "ショバ" ], "comment": "場所 (ばしょ): place, location, spot, position, room, space, basho, wrestling tournament\n所場 (しょば, ショバ): place (to run a business, e.g. street stall), place (to run a business, e.g. street stall)"},
 { "question": "女場記内芸", "answers": [ "場内", "じょうない" ], "comment": "場内 (じょうない): in-house, (on) the grounds, (in) the premises, hall, theatre, theater"},
 { "question": "肉大場術面", "answers": [ "場面", "ばめん" ], "comment": "場面 (ばめん): scene, setting (e.g. of novel)"},
 { "question": "気写色術半", "answers": [ "気色", "きしょく", "けしき", "色気", "いろけ" ], "comment": "気色 (きしょく, けしき): mood, humor, humour, looks, countenance, sign, indication\n色気 (いろけ): colouring, coloring, shade of colour, shade of color, sex appeal (esp. women), interest in the opposite sex, sensuality, seductiveness, glamor, glamour, sexual passion, romance, poetry, charm, desire, interest, inclination, ambition"},
 { "question": "紙足色安作", "answers": [ "色紙", "いろがみ", "しきし" ], "comment": "色紙 (いろがみ, しきし): coloured paper, colored paper, square fancy cardboard, used for autographs, poetry, etc."},
 { "question": "食器雨年歩", "answers": [ "食器", "しょっき" ], "comment": "食器 (しょっき): tableware"},
 { "question": "真数新食後", "answers": [ "食後", "しょくご" ], "comment": "食後 (しょくご): after a meal"},
 { "question": "白事集春食", "answers": [ "食事", "しょくじ" ], "comment": "食事 (しょくじ): meal, to eat"},
 { "question": "食科進見道", "answers": [ "食道", "しょくどう" ], "comment": "食道 (しょくどう): esophagus, gullet, esophageal"},
 { "question": "流手科肉食", "answers": [ "食肉", "しょくにく", "肉食", "にくしょく" ], "comment": "食肉 (しょくにく): meat (for consumption)\n肉食 (にくしょく): meat eating, eating of meat, meat diet, carnivorous"},
 { "question": "意物食記車", "answers": [ "食物", "しょくもつ", "くいもの" ], "comment": "食物 (しょくもつ, くいもの): food, foodstuff, food, foodstuff, prey, victim"},
 { "question": "食半配用行", "answers": [ "食用", "しょくよう" ], "comment": "食用 (しょくよう): for use as food, edible"},
 { "question": "行心肉集外", "answers": [ "心外", "しんがい", "外心", "がいしん" ], "comment": "心外 (しんがい): regrettable, vexing, upsetting, unthinkable, wholly unexpected\n外心 (がいしん): circumcenter, circumcentre, outer center, outer centre"},
 { "question": "進間心春身", "answers": [ "心身", "しんしん", "しんじん", "身心", "しんしん", "しんじん" ], "comment": "心身 (しんしん, しんじん): mind and body, mind and body\n身心 (しんしん, しんじん): mind and body, mind and body"},
 { "question": "心言出地半", "answers": [ "心地", "ここち", "地心", "ちしん", "心地", "しんじ" ], "comment": "心地 (ここち): feeling, sensation, mood, sensation of doing (usu. after -masu stem of verb)\n地心 (ちしん): center of the earth, centre of the earth\n心地 (しんじ): padding, lining, foundation"},
 { "question": "念歩後中心", "answers": [ "心中", "しんじゅう", "しんぢゅう", "中心", "ちゅうしん", "心中", "しんちゅう", "中心", "なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes"},
 { "question": "配代半心事", "answers": [ "心配事", "しんぱいごと" ], "comment": "心配事 (しんぱいごと): worries, cares, troubles"},
 { "question": "心月理進紙", "answers": [ "心理", "しんり" ], "comment": "心理 (しんり): state of mind, mentality, psychology"},
 { "question": "学給明心理", "answers": [ "心理学", "しんりがく" ], "comment": "心理学 (しんりがく): psychology"},
 { "question": "空外作会新", "answers": [ "新作", "しんさく" ], "comment": "新作 (しんさく): new work, new production"},
 { "question": "出元用車新", "answers": [ "新車", "しんしゃ" ], "comment": "新車 (しんしゃ): new car"},
 { "question": "手新日念目", "answers": [ "新手", "あらて", "しんて" ], "comment": "新手 (あらて, しんて): fresh supply of troops, newcomer, new method, new trick, fresh supply of troops, newcomer, new method, new trick"},
 { "question": "園実新人草", "answers": [ "新人", "しんじん" ], "comment": "新人 (しんじん): new face, newcomer, rookie, fresh recruit, modern humans (from Cro-Magnon man onwards)"},
 { "question": "元新数立生", "answers": [ "新生", "しんせい", "生新", "せいしん" ], "comment": "新生 (しんせい): rebirth, new birth, nascent\n生新 (せいしん): fresh, new"},
 { "question": "牛間新元体", "answers": [ "新体", "しんたい" ], "comment": "新体 (しんたい): new style"},
 { "question": "入草新重意", "answers": [ "新入", "しんにゅう" ], "comment": "新入 (しんにゅう): newly arrived, newly joined, newly entered"},
 { "question": "牛新命花年", "answers": [ "新年", "しんねん" ], "comment": "新年 (しんねん): New Year"},
 { "question": "代新徒分風", "answers": [ "新風", "しんぷう" ], "comment": "新風 (しんぷう): new style"},
 { "question": "意真番男学", "answers": [ "真意", "しんい" ], "comment": "真意 (しんい): real intention, true motive, true meaning"},
 { "question": "火番真空分", "answers": [ "真空", "しんくう" ], "comment": "真空 (しんくう): vacuum, hollow, empty"},
 { "question": "世音真身実", "answers": [ "真実", "しんじつ", "さな", "さね" ], "comment": "真実 (しんじつ, さな, さね): truth, reality, truth, reality, truth, reality"},
 { "question": "雨新心王真", "answers": [ "真心", "まごころ", "まこころ" ], "comment": "真心 (まごころ, まこころ): sincerity, devotion, sincerity, devotion"},
 { "question": "音真目配面", "answers": [ "真面目", "しんめんもく", "しんめんぼく", "まじめ" ], "comment": "真面目 (しんめんもく, しんめんぼく, まじめ): one's true character, one's true self, oneself, seriousness, earnestness, one's true character, one's true self, oneself, seriousness, earnestness, diligent, serious, honest, sober, grave, earnest, steady"},
 { "question": "夜重中真念", "answers": [ "真夜中", "まよなか" ], "comment": "真夜中 (まよなか): dead of night, midnight"},
 { "question": "声前真見理", "answers": [ "真理", "しんり" ], "comment": "真理 (しんり): truth"},
 { "question": "日念新親流", "answers": [ "親日", "しんにち" ], "comment": "親日 (しんにち): pro-Japanese"},
 { "question": "白親学分行", "answers": [ "親分", "おやぶん" ], "comment": "親分 (おやぶん): boss, kingpin, chief, head (e.g. of a crime syndicate)"},
 { "question": "身場時元行", "answers": [ "身元", "みもと" ], "comment": "身元 (みもと): person's identity, ID, past, background"},
 { "question": "身長国春紙", "answers": [ "身長", "しんちょう", "長身", "ちょうしん" ], "comment": "身長 (しんちょう): height (of body), stature\n長身 (ちょうしん): tall figure, high stature"},
 { "question": "内声紙身理", "answers": [ "身内", "みうち" ], "comment": "身内 (みうち): relatives, one's family, friends, members of the same organization, followers, henchmen, one's whole body"},
 { "question": "分身面牛発", "answers": [ "身分", "みぶん", "分身", "ぶんしん" ], "comment": "身分 (みぶん): social position, social status\n分身 (ぶんしん): parturition, delivery, one's child, branch, offshoot, one's other self"},
 { "question": "学体月進念", "answers": [ "進学", "しんがく" ], "comment": "進学 (しんがく): entering a higher-level school, esp. going on to university"},
 { "question": "面行雨花進", "answers": [ "行進", "こうしん", "進行", "しんこう" ], "comment": "行進 (こうしん): march, parade\n進行 (しんこう): moving forward (e.g. vehicle), onward movement, advance (work, procedure, etc), advancement, progress, progress (of a disease), disease progression, progression (harmonic, melodic)"},
 { "question": "雨出紙進元", "answers": [ "進出", "しんしゅつ" ], "comment": "進出 (しんしゅつ): advance (into a new market or stage of progress), launching (a new career or venture), expanding (into a new market), stepping forward, emerging"},
 { "question": "進入足番明", "answers": [ "進入", "しんにゅう" ], "comment": "進入 (しんにゅう): entry, approach, penetration"},
 { "question": "歩見進器面", "answers": [ "進歩", "しんぽ" ], "comment": "進歩 (しんぽ): progress, advance, improvement, development"},
 { "question": "人作夜格理", "answers": [ "人格", "じんかく" ], "comment": "人格 (じんかく): personality, character, individuality"},
 { "question": "給人所意間", "answers": [ "人間", "にんげん", "じんかん" ], "comment": "人間 (にんげん, じんかん): human being, person, man, mankind, humankind, character (of a person), the world"},
 { "question": "半写場人気", "answers": [ "人気", "にんき", "ひとけ", "じんき" ], "comment": "人気 (にんき, ひとけ, じんき): popularity, popular feeling, business conditions, sign of life, human presence, humanity, humaneness, prevailing mood of a locality, emotional climate of a district"},
 { "question": "事集進人作", "answers": [ "人事", "じんじ", "ひとごと" ], "comment": "人事 (じんじ, ひとごと): personnel affairs, human affairs, human resources, HR, other people's affairs, somebody else's problem, other people's affairs, somebody else's problem"},
 { "question": "出雨親集人", "answers": [ "人出", "ひとで" ], "comment": "人出 (ひとで): crowd, turnout"},
 { "question": "音生春草人", "answers": [ "人生", "じんせい" ], "comment": "人生 (じんせい): (human) life (i.e. conception to death)"},
 { "question": "園草人前明", "answers": [ "人前", "にんまえ", "ひとまえ", "前人", "ぜんじん" ], "comment": "人前 (にんまえ, ひとまえ): portion of food, the public, company\n前人 (ぜんじん): predecessor, former people"},
 { "question": "体牛記人夜", "answers": [ "人体", "じんたい", "じんてい", "にんてい" ], "comment": "人体 (じんたい, じんてい, にんてい): human body, personal appearance, looks, personal appearance, looks"},
 { "question": "給草理中人", "answers": [ "人中", "ひとなか", "中人", "ちゅうにん", "ちゅうじん", "人中", "じんちゅう", "にんちゅう", "中人", "なかびと", "なかひと" ], "comment": "人中 (ひとなか): society, company, the public, the world\n中人 (ちゅうにん, ちゅうじん): child in elementary or middle school, go-between, intermediary, middleman, mediator, intercessor, person of middling talent, strength, etc., middle-class person, bourgeois person, child in elementary or middle school, go-between, intermediary, middleman, mediator, intercessor, person of middling talent, strength, etc., middle-class person, bourgeois person\n人中 (じんちゅう, にんちゅう): in company, among people, philtrum, groove in the upper lip that runs from the bottom of the nose to the lip, in company, among people, philtrum, groove in the upper lip that runs from the bottom of the nose to the lip\n中人 (なかびと, なかひと): go-between, matchmaker, go-between, matchmaker, go-between, matchmaker"},
 { "question": "立道集人元", "answers": [ "人道", "じんどう", "にんどう" ], "comment": "人道 (じんどう, にんどう): humanity, sidewalk, footpath, human realm, humanity, sidewalk, footpath, human realm"},
 { "question": "物牛人場重", "answers": [ "人物", "じんぶつ" ], "comment": "人物 (じんぶつ): person, character, figure, personage, man, woman, one's character, one's personality, able person, talented person"},
 { "question": "男学人文科", "answers": [ "人文科学", "じんぶんかがく" ], "comment": "人文科学 (じんぶんかがく): humanities, social sciences, liberal arts"},
 { "question": "強集春人名", "answers": [ "人名", "じんめい", "名人", "めいじん" ], "comment": "人名 (じんめい): person's name\n名人 (めいじん): master, expert"},
 { "question": "牛命言人実", "answers": [ "人命", "じんめい" ], "comment": "人命 (じんめい): (human) life"},
 { "question": "言気集水世", "answers": [ "水気", "みずけ", "すいき" ], "comment": "水気 (みずけ, すいき): moisture, dampness, vapor, vapour, dropsy, edema, oedema, moisture, dampness, vapor, vapour, dropsy, edema, oedema"},
 { "question": "長水色徒意", "answers": [ "水色", "みずいろ" ], "comment": "水色 (みずいろ): light blue"},
 { "question": "道中写器水", "answers": [ "中水道", "ちゅうすいどう" ], "comment": "中水道 (ちゅうすいどう): gray-water system, grey-water system, recycled waste-water"},
 { "question": "紙水道体集", "answers": [ "水道", "すいどう" ], "comment": "水道 (すいどう): water service, water supply"},
 { "question": "分水歩作園", "answers": [ "水分", "すいぶん" ], "comment": "水分 (すいぶん): water, liquid, fluid, moisture, humidity, sap, juice"},
 { "question": "面女番水念", "answers": [ "水面", "すいめん", "みなも" ], "comment": "水面 (すいめん, みなも): water's surface, water's surface"},
 { "question": "水立格力長", "answers": [ "水力", "すいりょく", "力水", "ちからみず" ], "comment": "水力 (すいりょく): hydraulic power, water power\n力水 (ちからみず): water offered to wrestlers just prior to a bout"},
 { "question": "数学作給写", "answers": [ "数学", "すうがく" ], "comment": "数学 (すうがく): mathematics, arithmetic"},
 { "question": "意数写園日", "answers": [ "数日", "すうじつ", "日数", "にっすう", "ひかず" ], "comment": "数日 (すうじつ): few days\n日数 (にっすう, ひかず): a number of days, a number of days"},
 { "question": "明花間科世", "answers": [ "世間", "せけん" ], "comment": "世間 (せけん): world, society"},
 { "question": "世代風給生", "answers": [ "世代", "せだい" ], "comment": "世代 (せだい): generation, the world, the age"},
 { "question": "気生親芸意", "answers": [ "生意気", "なまいき" ], "comment": "生意気 (なまいき): impertinent, saucy, cheeky, conceit, audacious, brazen, feisty"},
 { "question": "春後白芸生", "answers": [ "後生", "こうせい", "ごしょう", "生後", "せいご" ], "comment": "後生 (こうせい, ごしょう): younger people, future generations, afterlife\n生後 (せいご): post-natal, since birth"},
 { "question": "生前牛格火", "answers": [ "生前", "せいぜん", "前生", "ぜんしょう" ], "comment": "生前 (せいぜん): while alive, during one's lifetime\n前生 (ぜんしょう): previous existence"},
 { "question": "楽火間体生", "answers": [ "生体", "せいたい" ], "comment": "生体 (せいたい): organism, living body"},
 { "question": "風地術生科", "answers": [ "生地", "きじ", "せいち" ], "comment": "生地 (きじ, せいち): cloth, fabric, material, texture, one's true character, unglazed pottery, uncooked dough, batter, birthplace"},
 { "question": "歩長明生本", "answers": [ "生長", "せいちょう", "長生", "ちょうせい" ], "comment": "生長 (せいちょう): growth, increment\n長生 (ちょうせい): longevity"},
 { "question": "世徒草生集", "answers": [ "生徒", "せいと" ], "comment": "生徒 (せいと): pupil"},
 { "question": "月生声年日", "answers": [ "生年月日", "せいねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "生年月日 (せいねんがっぴ): birth date, date of birth, DOB"},
 { "question": "体生物空明", "answers": [ "生物体", "せいぶつたい" ], "comment": "生物体 (せいぶつたい): organism"},
 { "question": "手声学生物", "answers": [ "生物学", "せいぶつがく" ], "comment": "生物学 (せいぶつがく): biology"},
 { "question": "夜体時生命", "answers": [ "生命体", "せいめいたい" ], "comment": "生命体 (せいめいたい): life-form"},
 { "question": "生理給安番", "answers": [ "生理", "せいり" ], "comment": "生理 (せいり): physiology, menstruation, one's period, menses"},
 { "question": "見楽元王声", "answers": [ "声楽", "せいがく" ], "comment": "声楽 (せいがく): vocal music"},
 { "question": "力安声空明", "answers": [ "声明", "せいめい", "しょうみょう" ], "comment": "声明 (せいめい, しょうみょう): declaration, statement, proclamation, sabdavidya (ancient Indian linguistic and grammatical studies), chanting of Buddhist hymns (usu. in Sanskrit or Chinese)"},
 { "question": "国先安親雨", "answers": [ "先安", "さきやす" ], "comment": "先安 (さきやす): lower future quotations"},
 { "question": "重術和月先", "answers": [ "先月", "せんげつ" ], "comment": "先月 (せんげつ): last month"},
 { "question": "見先草入車", "answers": [ "先入見", "せんにゅうけん" ], "comment": "先入見 (せんにゅうけん): preconception, prejudice, preoccupation"},
 { "question": "理重雨行先", "answers": [ "行先", "いきさき", "ゆきさき", "先行", "せんこう" ], "comment": "行先 (いきさき, ゆきさき): destination, whereabouts, address, destination, whereabouts, address\n先行 (せんこう): preceding, going first, leading, going ahead, taking priority"},
 { "question": "世先手地集", "answers": [ "手先", "てさき", "先手", "さきて", "せんて" ], "comment": "手先 (てさき): fingers, underling, stooge, subordinate, pawn\n先手 (さきて, せんて): front lines, vanguard, first move (in go, shogi, etc.), moving first, person with the first move, forestalling, (seizing the) initiative"},
 { "question": "先半名重進", "answers": [ "先進", "せんしん" ], "comment": "先進 (せんしん): seniority, advance, leadership"},
 { "question": "間国所先進", "answers": [ "先進国", "せんしんこく" ], "comment": "先進国 (せんしんこく): advanced (developed) country, advanced nations"},
 { "question": "先人術記親", "answers": [ "先人", "せんじん" ], "comment": "先人 (せんじん): predecessor, pioneer, ancestor"},
 { "question": "生給先心草", "answers": [ "先生", "せんせい", "せんじょう", "シーサン" ], "comment": "先生 (せんせい, せんじょう, シーサン): teacher, master, doctor, with names of teachers, etc. as an honorific, previous existence, teacher, master, doctor, with names of teachers, etc. as an honorific, previous existence, boy"},
 { "question": "草面心代先", "answers": [ "先代", "せんだい" ], "comment": "先代 (せんだい): family predecessor, previous age, previous generation"},
 { "question": "先格日実集", "answers": [ "先日", "せんじつ" ], "comment": "先日 (せんじつ): the other day, a few days ago"},
 { "question": "雨発草先合", "answers": [ "先発", "せんぱつ" ], "comment": "先発 (せんぱつ): starting in advance, starting first, going first, going ahead, starting (in team sports)"},
 { "question": "先記物声国", "answers": [ "先物", "さきもの" ], "comment": "先物 (さきもの): futures"},
 { "question": "体歩前心記", "answers": [ "前記", "ぜんき" ], "comment": "前記 (ぜんき): aforesaid, above-mentioned, said, above"},
 { "question": "後内和前草", "answers": [ "前後", "ぜんご", "まえしりえ" ], "comment": "前後 (ぜんご, まえしりえ): front and rear, front and back, before and behind, back and forth, before and after, order, context, consequences, inversion, reversion, getting out of order, co-occurring, around, about, approximately, nearly, front and rear, front and back, before and behind"},
 { "question": "力前身歩真", "answers": [ "前身", "ぜんしん" ], "comment": "前身 (ぜんしん): antecedents, ancestor, previous position, previous existence, predecessor organization, predecessor organisation"},
 { "question": "写進明力前", "answers": [ "前進力", "ぜんしんりょく" ], "comment": "前進力 (ぜんしんりょく): driving power"},
 { "question": "日前心牛流", "answers": [ "前日", "ぜんじつ", "まえび" ], "comment": "前日 (ぜんじつ, まえび): previous day, day before, eve, prior day, preceding day, previous day, day before, eve, prior day, preceding day"},
 { "question": "園年徒前写", "answers": [ "前年", "ぜんねん" ], "comment": "前年 (ぜんねん): the preceding year, the previous year, last year"},
 { "question": "先文前格写", "answers": [ "前文", "ぜんぶん" ], "comment": "前文 (ぜんぶん): preamble, the above statement"},
 { "question": "面見前新安", "answers": [ "前面", "ぜんめん", "面前", "めんぜん" ], "comment": "前面 (ぜんめん): front part, frontage, facade, initial pledge (e.g. election), opening slogan\n面前 (めんぜん): presence"},
 { "question": "念夜国前所", "answers": [ "前夜", "ぜんや", "夜前", "やぜん" ], "comment": "前夜 (ぜんや): last night, the previous night, night before (Christmas, etc.), eve (of festival, major event, etc.)\n夜前 (やぜん): last night"},
 { "question": "草白数花牛", "answers": [ "草花", "くさばな", "そうか" ], "comment": "草花 (くさばな, そうか): flower, flowering plant, flower, flowering plant"},
 { "question": "男足外配音", "answers": [ "足音", "あしおと" ], "comment": "足音 (あしおと): footsteps (sound)"},
 { "question": "命場足真年", "answers": [ "足場", "あしば" ], "comment": "足場 (あしば): scaffold, scaffolding, foothold, footing, foothold (e.g. in business), foundation, base, convenience for transportation, convenience of access (by road or rail)"},
 { "question": "空園格強体", "answers": [ "体格", "たいかく" ], "comment": "体格 (たいかく): physique, constitution"},
 { "question": "体進牛芸重", "answers": [ "体重", "たいじゅう", "重体", "じゅうたい" ], "comment": "体重 (たいじゅう): body weight, one's weight\n重体 (じゅうたい): seriously ill, serious condition, critical state"},
 { "question": "長代体水見", "answers": [ "体長", "たいちょう" ], "comment": "体長 (たいちょう): length of an animal (sometimes including and sometimes excluding the tail)"},
 { "question": "体雨番前内", "answers": [ "体内", "たいない" ], "comment": "体内 (たいない): interior of the body"},
 { "question": "力命時月体", "answers": [ "体力", "たいりょく" ], "comment": "体力 (たいりょく): stamina, endurance, physical strength, resilience, resistance to disease, strength of an organization (e.g. profitability, productivity, economic clout, stability, growth potential)"},
 { "question": "春行代安声", "answers": [ "代行", "だいこう" ], "comment": "代行 (だいこう): acting as agent"},
 { "question": "王代人写給", "answers": [ "代人", "だいにん" ], "comment": "代人 (だいにん): substitute, deputy, proxy, representative, agent"},
 { "question": "代用草記肉", "answers": [ "代用肉", "だいようにく" ], "comment": "代用肉 (だいようにく): meat substitute"},
 { "question": "代歩白給理", "answers": [ "代理", "だいり" ], "comment": "代理 (だいり): representation, agency, proxy, deputy, agent, attorney, substitute, alternate, acting (principal, etc.)"},
 { "question": "元草心大雨", "answers": [ "大雨", "おおあめ" ], "comment": "大雨 (おおあめ): heavy rain"},
 { "question": "夜大事火春", "answers": [ "大火事", "おおかじ" ], "comment": "大火事 (おおかじ): big fire (buildings, etc. on fire)"},
 { "question": "写大元世会", "answers": [ "大会", "たいかい" ], "comment": "大会 (たいかい): convention, tournament, mass meeting, rally"},
 { "question": "面春学大流", "answers": [ "大学", "だいがく" ], "comment": "大学 (だいがく): post-secondary education institution, incl. university, college, etc., former central university of Kyoto (established under the ritsuryo system for the training of government administrators), the Great Learning (one of the Four Books)"},
 { "question": "生大学元春", "answers": [ "大学生", "だいがくせい" ], "comment": "大学生 (だいがくせい): university student, college student"},
 { "question": "世入番気大", "answers": [ "大気", "たいき" ], "comment": "大気 (たいき): atmosphere"},
 { "question": "進紙月大空", "answers": [ "大空", "おおぞら" ], "comment": "大空 (おおぞら): heavens, firmament, sky"},
 { "question": "間後実大国", "answers": [ "国大", "こくだい", "大国", "たいこく" ], "comment": "国大 (こくだい): national university\n大国 (たいこく): large country, major powers"},
 { "question": "大作科歩春", "answers": [ "大作", "たいさく" ], "comment": "大作 (たいさく): epic"},
 { "question": "大配肉事新", "answers": [ "事大", "じだい", "大事", "だいじ", "おおごと" ], "comment": "事大 (じだい): subserviency to the stronger\n大事 (だいじ, おおごと): important, valuable, serious matter, safe (Tochigi dialect), OK, important, valuable, serious matter, safe (Tochigi dialect), OK"},
 { "question": "手大紙明時", "answers": [ "大手紙", "おおてし" ], "comment": "大手紙 (おおてし): major newspapers"},
 { "question": "人元進草大", "answers": [ "大人", "おとな", "だいにん", "たいじん" ], "comment": "大人 (おとな, だいにん, たいじん): adult, adult, man of substance or virtue, gentleman, giant, adult"},
 { "question": "後水大内交", "answers": [ "大水", "おおみず" ], "comment": "大水 (おおみず): flood"},
 { "question": "春園声紙大", "answers": [ "大声", "おおごえ", "たいせい" ], "comment": "大声 (おおごえ, たいせい): loud voice, loud voice"},
 { "question": "大楽写体世", "answers": [ "大体", "だいたい" ], "comment": "大体 (だいたい): outline, main point, gist, general, substantially, approximately, about, in the first place, to begin with, from the start"},
 { "question": "後交集大地", "answers": [ "大地", "だいち" ], "comment": "大地 (だいち): ground, earth, the solid earth, the (vast) land"},
 { "question": "写大見半新", "answers": [ "大半", "たいはん" ], "comment": "大半 (たいはん): majority, more than half, most (of), mostly, largely, mainly, predominately, nearly"},
 { "question": "大物夜集元", "answers": [ "大物", "おおもの" ], "comment": "大物 (おおもの): important person, big-shot, bigwig, big game (animal, fish), big thing, valuable thing"},
 { "question": "大番草分給", "answers": [ "大分", "だいぶ", "だいぶん" ], "comment": "大分 (だいぶ, だいぶん): considerably, greatly, a lot, considerably, greatly, a lot"},
 { "question": "世歩先大名", "answers": [ "大名", "だいみょう" ], "comment": "大名 (だいみょう): daimyo (Japanese feudal lord), daimio"},
 { "question": "女男格肉国", "answers": [ "男女", "だんじょ", "なんにょ", "おとこおんな", "女男", "おんなおとこ" ], "comment": "男女 (だんじょ, なんにょ, おとこおんな): men and women, man and woman, both sexes, both genders, men and women, man and woman, both sexes, both genders, masculine woman, mannish woman, feminine man, effeminate man, intersexual, hermaphrodite\n女男 (おんなおとこ): feminine man, effeminate man, masculine woman, mannish woman"},
 { "question": "前男命器写", "answers": [ "男前", "おとこまえ" ], "comment": "男前 (おとこまえ): handsome man"},
 { "question": "肉地行元世", "answers": [ "地元", "じもと" ], "comment": "地元 (じもと): home area, home town, local"},
 { "question": "術写地春道", "answers": [ "地道", "じみち" ], "comment": "地道 (じみち): steady, honest, sober, straightforward"},
 { "question": "長念名食地", "answers": [ "地名", "ちめい" ], "comment": "地名 (ちめい): place name"},
 { "question": "春科地言面", "answers": [ "地面", "じめん" ], "comment": "地面 (じめん): ground, earth's surface"},
 { "question": "風交時理地", "answers": [ "地理", "ちり" ], "comment": "地理 (ちり): geography"},
 { "question": "年所牛学中", "answers": [ "中学年", "ちゅうがくねん" ], "comment": "中学年 (ちゅうがくねん): middle grades of primary school (third and fourth grades)"},
 { "question": "中白給生学", "answers": [ "中学生", "ちゅうがくせい" ], "comment": "中学生 (ちゅうがくせい): junior high school student, middle school pupil"},
 { "question": "間中徒場白", "answers": [ "間中", "あいだじゅう", "中間", "ちゅうかん", "ちゅうげん" ], "comment": "間中 (あいだじゅう): during\n中間 (ちゅうかん, ちゅうげん): middle, midway, interim, samurai's attendant, footman"},
 { "question": "中言色元歩", "answers": [ "中元", "ちゅうげん", "元中", "げんちゅう" ], "comment": "中元 (ちゅうげん): 15th day of the 7th lunar month, (last day of) Bon lantern festival, mid-year gift, summer gift, Bon Festival gifts\n元中 (げんちゅう): Genchuu era (of the Southern Court) (1384.4.28-1392.10.5)"},
 { "question": "草親国中重", "answers": [ "国中", "くにじゅう", "こくじゅう", "こくちゅう", "中国", "ちゅうごく" ], "comment": "国中 (くにじゅう, こくじゅう, こくちゅう): all over the country, all over the country, all over the country\n中国 (ちゅうごく): China, Chugoku region of western Honshu (incl. Okayama, Hiroshima, Shimane, Tottori and Yamaguchi prefectures), central part of a country, main region"},
 { "question": "紙人中実国", "answers": [ "中国人", "ちゅうごくじん" ], "comment": "中国人 (ちゅうごくじん): Chinese person"},
 { "question": "中心面大念", "answers": [ "心中", "しんじゅう", "しんぢゅう", "中心", "ちゅうしん", "心中", "しんちゅう", "中心", "なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes"},
 { "question": "中花面世記", "answers": [ "中世", "ちゅうせい" ], "comment": "中世 (ちゅうせい): Middle Ages (in Japan esp. the Kamakura and Muromachi periods ), medieval times, mediaeval times"},
 { "question": "前中発白実", "answers": [ "中前", "ちゅうぜん" ], "comment": "中前 (ちゅうぜん): front of center field, front of centre field"},
 { "question": "道安時実中", "answers": [ "中道", "ちゅうどう", "道中", "どうちゅう", "中道", "なかみち" ], "comment": "中道 (ちゅうどう): middle of the road, moderation, golden mean, the middle (of what one is doing), half-way, middle way, middle path\n道中 (どうちゅう): along the way, journey\n中道 (なかみち): road through the middle, middle road"},
 { "question": "日牛念中紙", "answers": [ "中日", "ちゅうにち", "なかび", "日中", "にっちゅう", "ひなか" ], "comment": "中日 (ちゅうにち, なかび): China and Japan, the middle day, the equinoctial day, middle day (e.g sumo tournament, run of theatrical performances, etc.)\n日中 (にっちゅう, ひなか): daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese, daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese"},
 { "question": "中年重発面", "answers": [ "中年", "ちゅうねん", "年中", "ねんじゅう", "ねんちゅう", "ねんぢゅう" ], "comment": "中年 (ちゅうねん): middle-age, middle age, midlife, one's middle years\n年中 (ねんじゅう, ねんちゅう, ねんぢゅう): whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.), whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.), whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.)"},
 { "question": "合中紙安立", "answers": [ "中立", "ちゅうりつ", "なかだち" ], "comment": "中立 (ちゅうりつ, なかだち): neutrality, break between the light meal and the actual serving of tea (during a formal tea ceremony)"},
 { "question": "理器場流中", "answers": [ "中流", "ちゅうりゅう" ], "comment": "中流 (ちゅうりゅう): mid-stream, middle course, middle class"},
 { "question": "歩中和念給", "answers": [ "中和", "ちゅうわ" ], "comment": "中和 (ちゅうわ): neutralizing, neutralising, counteracting, neutral, unbiased"},
 { "question": "間場長火時", "answers": [ "長時間", "ちょうじかん" ], "comment": "長時間 (ちょうじかん): long period of time, long playing"},
 { "question": "長器世所白", "answers": [ "所長", "しょちょう", "長所", "ちょうしょ" ], "comment": "所長 (しょちょう): chief, head (of an office, of a laboratory)\n長所 (ちょうしょ): strong point, merit, virtue, advantage"},
 { "question": "長安地女進", "answers": [ "長女", "ちょうじょ" ], "comment": "長女 (ちょうじょ): eldest daughter, first-born daughter"},
 { "question": "男集術長草", "answers": [ "長男", "ちょうなん" ], "comment": "長男 (ちょうなん): eldest son (may be the only son), first-born son"},
 { "question": "草入年白長", "answers": [ "長年", "ながねん", "年長", "ねんちょう" ], "comment": "長年 (ながねん): long time, many years, long time, many years\n年長 (ねんちょう): seniority"},
 { "question": "歩身実徒水", "answers": [ "徒歩", "とほ", "かち" ], "comment": "徒歩 (とほ, かち): walking, going on foot, foot soldier (Edo period), samurai on foot, going on foot, walking"},
 { "question": "肉言場和道", "answers": [ "道場", "どうじょう" ], "comment": "道場 (どうじょう): dojo (hall used for martial arts training), manda (place of Buddhist practice or meditation, esp. the place under the bodhi tree where Buddha attained enlightenment)"},
 { "question": "道理時写言", "answers": [ "道理", "どうり" ], "comment": "道理 (どうり): reason, truth"},
 { "question": "長内徒牛科", "answers": [ "内科", "ないか" ], "comment": "内科 (ないか): internal medicine, i.e. treatment by medical procedures rather than surgical procedures, department of internal medicine (hospital, etc.)"},
 { "question": "気足内記世", "answers": [ "内気", "うちき" ], "comment": "内気 (うちき): bashfulness, shyness, reserve, timidity"},
 { "question": "実内世音念", "answers": [ "内実", "ないじつ" ], "comment": "内実 (ないじつ): the facts"},
 { "question": "心集作目内", "answers": [ "内心", "ないしん" ], "comment": "内心 (ないしん): innermost thoughts, real intention, inmost heart, one's mind, in the heart, inner center (centre)"},
 { "question": "内中大歩面", "answers": [ "内面", "ないめん", "うちづら" ], "comment": "内面 (ないめん, うちづら): inside, interior, the face one presents at home"},
 { "question": "食肉身芸雨", "answers": [ "食肉", "しょくにく", "肉食", "にくしょく" ], "comment": "食肉 (しょくにく): meat (for consumption)\n肉食 (にくしょく): meat eating, eating of meat, meat diet, carnivorous"},
 { "question": "命見肉科親", "answers": [ "肉親", "にくしん" ], "comment": "肉親 (にくしん): blood relationship, blood relative"},
 { "question": "代体肉徒紙", "answers": [ "肉体", "にくたい" ], "comment": "肉体 (にくたい): the body, the flesh"},
 { "question": "雨日園記術", "answers": [ "日記", "にっき" ], "comment": "日記 (にっき): diary, journal"},
 { "question": "時番紙年日", "answers": [ "日時", "にちじ", "時日", "じじつ" ], "comment": "日時 (にちじ): date and time\n時日 (じじつ): date, time"},
 { "question": "発日雨食牛", "answers": [ "日食", "にっしょく" ], "comment": "日食 (にっしょく): solar eclipse"},
 { "question": "念場格日中", "answers": [ "中日", "ちゅうにち", "なかび", "日中", "にっちゅう", "ひなか" ], "comment": "中日 (ちゅうにち, なかび): China and Japan, the middle day, the equinoctial day, middle day (e.g sumo tournament, run of theatrical performances, etc.)\n日中 (にっちゅう, ひなか): daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese, daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese"},
 { "question": "人実本男日", "answers": [ "日本人", "にほんじん", "にっぽんじん" ], "comment": "日本人 (にほんじん, にっぽんじん): Japanese person, Japanese people, Japanese person, Japanese people"},
 { "question": "王夜言理日", "answers": [ "日夜", "にちや" ], "comment": "日夜 (にちや): day and night, always"},
 { "question": "心日場和行", "answers": [ "日和", "ひより", "びより" ], "comment": "日和 (ひより, びより): weather, climatic conditions, fine weather, clear day, situation, state of affairs, sea conditions, good day for sailing, ideal weather (for some action, event, etc.), perfect day"},
 { "question": "音園入春真", "answers": [ "入園", "にゅうえん" ], "comment": "入園 (にゅうえん): enrollment in kindergarten, enrolment in kindergarten, entering a park, garden, zoo, etc."},
 { "question": "入給学間重", "answers": [ "入学", "にゅうがく" ], "comment": "入学 (にゅうがく): entry to school or university, matriculation, enrolment (in university, etc.)"},
 { "question": "夜見入国牛", "answers": [ "入国", "にゅうこく", "にゅうごく" ], "comment": "入国 (にゅうこく, にゅうごく): entry to a country, entry to a country"},
 { "question": "科給入手言", "answers": [ "入手", "にゅうしゅ" ], "comment": "入手 (にゅうしゅ): acquisition, obtaining, coming to hand"},
 { "question": "入芸所肉半", "answers": [ "入所", "にゅうしょ" ], "comment": "入所 (にゅうしょ): admission (e.g. to a training institution, research establishment, social welfare facility, etc.), entrance, imprisonment, internment, confinement"},
 { "question": "場入車女命", "answers": [ "入場", "にゅうじょう" ], "comment": "入場 (にゅうじょう): entrance, admission, entering"},
 { "question": "念安入体番", "answers": [ "入念", "にゅうねん" ], "comment": "入念 (にゅうねん): careful, elaborate, scrupulous"},
 { "question": "発番器入力", "answers": [ "入力", "にゅうりょく" ], "comment": "入力 (にゅうりょく): input, (data) entry"},
 { "question": "王年歩会気", "answers": [ "年会", "ねんかい" ], "comment": "年会 (ねんかい): conference, annual convention"},
 { "question": "火間年身写", "answers": [ "年間", "ねんかん" ], "comment": "年間 (ねんかん): years (period of)"},
 { "question": "月日意年紙", "answers": [ "年月日", "ねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "年月日 (ねんがっぴ): date"},
 { "question": "肉徒数年国", "answers": [ "数年", "すうねん", "年数", "ねんすう" ], "comment": "数年 (すうねん): several years\n年数 (ねんすう): number of years"},
 { "question": "和雨手年生", "answers": [ "生年", "せいねん", "年生", "ねんせい" ], "comment": "生年 (せいねん): the year of a person's birth, age\n年生 (ねんせい): pupil in ... year, student in ... year"},
 { "question": "風器安年代", "answers": [ "年代", "ねんだい" ], "comment": "年代 (ねんだい): age, era, period, date"},
 { "question": "科食進男年", "answers": [ "年男", "としおとこ" ], "comment": "年男 (としおとこ): Man of the Year, referring to a man born in a year with the same Chinese zodiac sign as the current year"},
 { "question": "園女中時年", "answers": [ "中年女", "ちゅうねんおんな" ], "comment": "中年女 (ちゅうねんおんな): middle-aged woman"},
 { "question": "春草集年長", "answers": [ "長年", "ながねん", "年長", "ねんちょう" ], "comment": "長年 (ながねん): long time, many years, long time, many years\n年長 (ねんちょう): seniority"},
 { "question": "内年立徒記", "answers": [ "年内", "ねんない" ], "comment": "年内 (ねんない): by the end of the year"},
 { "question": "年配作花歩", "answers": [ "年配", "ねんぱい" ], "comment": "年配 (ねんぱい): elderly, age, years"},
 { "question": "日格念番力", "answers": [ "念力", "ねんりき" ], "comment": "念力 (ねんりき): will-power, faith, telekinesis, psychokinesis"},
 { "question": "内元給配人", "answers": [ "配給", "はいきゅう" ], "comment": "配給 (はいきゅう): distribution (e.g. films, rice), rationing (e.g. food, gasoline), food ration"},
 { "question": "発草分術配", "answers": [ "配分", "はいぶん", "分配", "ぶんぱい" ], "comment": "配分 (はいぶん): distribution, allotment\n分配 (ぶんぱい): division, splitting, sharing, distribution, dissemination, allocation"},
 { "question": "中徒紙園白", "answers": [ "白紙", "はくし", "しらかみ" ], "comment": "白紙 (はくし, しらかみ): white paper, flyleaf, blank paper, clean slate, lack of prior opinion, positions, etc., scratch, beginning, white paper, flyleaf, blank paper, clean slate, lack of prior opinion, positions, etc., scratch, beginning"},
 { "question": "給分強人白", "answers": [ "白人", "はくじん" ], "comment": "白人 (はくじん): white person, Caucasian"},
 { "question": "発音牛前用", "answers": [ "発音", "はつおん" ], "comment": "発音 (はつおん): pronunciation"},
 { "question": "火国発夜芸", "answers": [ "発火", "はっか" ], "comment": "発火 (はっか): ignition, catching fire, firing (e.g. gun), discharging"},
 { "question": "真食発見重", "answers": [ "発見", "はっけん" ], "comment": "発見 (はっけん): discovery, detection, finding"},
 { "question": "発楽配言科", "answers": [ "発言", "はつげん" ], "comment": "発言 (はつげん): statement, remark, observation, utterance, speech, proposal"},
 { "question": "行元春発外", "answers": [ "発行", "はっこう" ], "comment": "発行 (はっこう): issue (publications), publishing, raising an event (software)"},
 { "question": "牛発作集日", "answers": [ "発作", "ほっさ" ], "comment": "発作 (ほっさ): fit, spasm, attack, seizure"},
 { "question": "車発真草分", "answers": [ "発車", "はっしゃ" ], "comment": "発車 (はっしゃ): departure of a vehicle"},
 { "question": "生目強術発", "answers": [ "発生", "はっせい" ], "comment": "発生 (はっせい): outbreak, spring forth, occurrence, incidence, generation (e.g. of power or heat), genesis, origin, ontogeny, development of complex multicellular structures from cell(s) in a simple state"},
 { "question": "科発念声花", "answers": [ "発声", "はっせい" ], "comment": "発声 (はっせい): utterance, speaking, vocalization, vocalisation, enunciation, pronouncing, leading a group of people (in cheering, singing, etc.)"},
 { "question": "明命発重間", "answers": [ "発明", "はつめい" ], "comment": "発明 (はつめい): invention, intelligent, clever, being enlightened, having the meaning of everything become clear"},
 { "question": "半言身科牛", "answers": [ "半身", "はんしん", "はんみ" ], "comment": "半身 (はんしん, はんみ): half the body, half length, stance with legs in an L-shape, with one leg bent in front and other extended behind (martial arts, traditional theater)"},
 { "question": "半集数記言", "answers": [ "半数", "はんすう" ], "comment": "半数 (はんすう): half the number, haploid"},
 { "question": "半器生強科", "answers": [ "半生", "はんしょう", "はんせい", "生半", "なまなか" ], "comment": "半生 (はんしょう, はんせい): half death, half a lifetime\n生半 (なまなか): halfway-done, mediocre, uncertain, half-hearted, half-heartedly, insufficiently"},
 { "question": "分番風半器", "answers": [ "半分", "はんぶん", "はんぷん" ], "comment": "半分 (はんぶん, はんぷん): half, half minute"},
 { "question": "牛半面空心", "answers": [ "半面", "はんめん" ], "comment": "半面 (はんめん): half the face, one side, half, the other side, the reverse, the contrary"},
 { "question": "地写日牛番", "answers": [ "番地", "ばんち", "地番", "ちばん" ], "comment": "番地 (ばんち): house number, address\n地番 (ちばん): lot number"},
 { "question": "目肉世道番", "answers": [ "番目", "ばんめ" ], "comment": "番目 (ばんめ): indicates position in a sequence, divisions of a kabuki performance"},
 { "question": "風間念格身", "answers": [ "風格", "ふうかく" ], "comment": "風格 (ふうかく): personality, style, appearance"},
 { "question": "白園風流番", "answers": [ "風流", "ふうりゅう" ], "comment": "風流 (ふうりゅう): elegance, taste, refinement"},
 { "question": "間風楽心力", "answers": [ "風力", "ふうりょく" ], "comment": "風力 (ふうりょく): wind power, force (level on the Beaufort wind speed scale)"},
 { "question": "音学交目物", "answers": [ "物音", "ものおと", "音物", "いんもつ", "いんぶつ" ], "comment": "物音 (ものおと): sounds\n音物 (いんもつ, いんぶつ): present (to build up a \"friendship\" with someone), bribe, present (to build up a \"friendship\" with someone), bribe"},
 { "question": "集重念物事", "answers": [ "事物", "じぶつ", "物事", "ものごと" ], "comment": "事物 (じぶつ): things, affairs\n物事 (ものごと): things, everything"},
 { "question": "立心物歩元", "answers": [ "物心", "ものごころ", "ぶっしん" ], "comment": "物心 (ものごころ, ぶっしん): awareness of things around one, ability to understand what is going on around oneself, judgment, judgement, discretion, matter and mind"},
 { "question": "足写物記体", "answers": [ "物体", "ぶったい", "もったい" ], "comment": "物体 (ぶったい, もったい): body, object, superior airs, air of importance, overemphasis"},
 { "question": "新世物理国", "answers": [ "物理", "ぶつり" ], "comment": "物理 (ぶつり): physics, law of nature"},
 { "question": "所身物学理", "answers": [ "物理学", "ぶつりがく" ], "comment": "物理学 (ぶつりがく): physics"},
 { "question": "会器事科分", "answers": [ "分科会", "ぶんかかい" ], "comment": "分科会 (ぶんかかい): subcommittee, subworking group"},
 { "question": "物身意道分", "answers": [ "身分", "みぶん", "分身", "ぶんしん" ], "comment": "身分 (みぶん): social position, social status\n分身 (ぶんしん): parturition, delivery, one's child, branch, offshoot, one's other self"},
 { "question": "交真器分数", "answers": [ "真分数", "しんぶんすう" ], "comment": "真分数 (しんぶんすう): proper fraction"},
 { "question": "雨命入配分", "answers": [ "配分", "はいぶん", "分配", "ぶんぱい" ], "comment": "配分 (はいぶん): distribution, allotment\n分配 (ぶんぱい): division, splitting, sharing, distribution, dissemination, allocation"},
 { "question": "後草給立分", "answers": [ "分立", "ぶんりつ" ], "comment": "分立 (ぶんりつ): segregation, separation, independence"},
 { "question": "記文科数新", "answers": [ "文科", "ぶんか" ], "comment": "文科 (ぶんか): literary course, the arts"},
 { "question": "国用新学文", "answers": [ "国文学", "こくぶんがく" ], "comment": "国文学 (こくぶんがく): Japanese literature"},
 { "question": "文新立徒楽", "answers": [ "文楽", "ぶんらく" ], "comment": "文楽 (ぶんらく): Japanese puppet theatre (theater), bunraku"},
 { "question": "文芸進間給", "answers": [ "文芸", "ぶんげい", "芸文", "げいぶん" ], "comment": "文芸 (ぶんげい): literature, art and literature, belles-lettres\n芸文 (げいぶん): art and literature"},
 { "question": "文雨体出王", "answers": [ "文体", "ぶんたい", "体文", "たいもん" ], "comment": "文体 (ぶんたい): literary style\n体文 (たいもん): consonant (in the Siddham script)"},
 { "question": "内中文草歩", "answers": [ "文中", "ぶんちゅう", "中文", "ちゅうぶん" ], "comment": "文中 (ぶんちゅう): in the document, Bunchuu era (of the Southern Court) (1372.4.?-1375.5.27)\n中文 (ちゅうぶん): Chinese language (written), Chinese literature"},
 { "question": "場明心器文", "answers": [ "文明", "ぶんめい", "明文", "めいぶん" ], "comment": "文明 (ぶんめい): civilization, civilisation, culture, Bummei era (1469.4.28-1487.7.20)\n明文 (めいぶん): explicit statement (e.g. law), express provision"},
 { "question": "女文火面夜", "answers": [ "文面", "ぶんめん" ], "comment": "文面 (ぶんめん): content of a letter"},
 { "question": "行親足科歩", "answers": [ "歩行", "ほこう", "かち" ], "comment": "歩行 (ほこう, かち): walk, foot soldier (Edo period), samurai on foot, going on foot, walking"},
 { "question": "車合世歩用", "answers": [ "歩合", "ぶあい" ], "comment": "歩合 (ぶあい): rate, ratio, commission, percentage, poundage"},
 { "question": "道目時配歩", "answers": [ "歩道", "ほどう" ], "comment": "歩道 (ほどう): footpath, walkway, sidewalk"},
 { "question": "牛女火音本", "answers": [ "本音", "ほんね" ], "comment": "本音 (ほんね): real intention, motive, true opinion, what one really thinks"},
 { "question": "発立親本格", "answers": [ "本格", "ほんかく" ], "comment": "本格 (ほんかく): original method or procedure, serious, orthodox, classical, genuine"},
 { "question": "園理本気車", "answers": [ "本気", "ほんき" ], "comment": "本気 (ほんき): seriousness, earnestness, truth, sanctity"},
 { "question": "本理記国行", "answers": [ "本国", "ほんごく", "国本", "こくほん" ], "comment": "本国 (ほんごく): one's own country\n国本 (こくほん): foundation of the nation"},
 { "question": "本紙夜実重", "answers": [ "本紙", "ほんし" ], "comment": "本紙 (ほんし): this newspaper"},
 { "question": "器空本念場", "answers": [ "本場", "ほんば" ], "comment": "本場 (ほんば): home, habitat, center, centre, best place, authentic, genuine"},
 { "question": "半火本心進", "answers": [ "本心", "ほんしん" ], "comment": "本心 (ほんしん): true feelings"},
 { "question": "人器実所本", "answers": [ "本人", "ほんにん" ], "comment": "本人 (ほんにん): the person himself"},
 { "question": "本声数集事", "answers": [ "本数", "ほんすう" ], "comment": "本数 (ほんすう): number of long thin objects (movies, TV programs, baseball games, etc.) (programmes)"},
 { "question": "白本体器牛", "answers": [ "本体", "ほんたい", "ほんだい" ], "comment": "本体 (ほんたい, ほんだい): substance, real form, main part, main unit, body (of a machine), this machine, this appliance, object of worship (at a shrine, temple, etc.), noumenon, base price, pre-tax price, substance, real form, main part, main unit, body (of a machine), this machine, this appliance, object of worship (at a shrine, temple, etc.), noumenon, base price, pre-tax price"},
 { "question": "発本日集国", "answers": [ "日本国", "にほんこく" ], "comment": "日本国 (にほんこく): Japan"},
 { "question": "牛芸本用年", "answers": [ "本年", "ほんねん" ], "comment": "本年 (ほんねん): this (current) year"},
 { "question": "親時面本番", "answers": [ "本番", "ほんばん" ], "comment": "本番 (ほんばん): performance, take, going before an audience or on-air, game, season, crucial moment, actual sexual intercourse (i.e. not simulated), penetration"},
 { "question": "物空親牛本", "answers": [ "本物", "ほんもの" ], "comment": "本物 (ほんもの): genuine article, real thing, real deal"},
 { "question": "世名立交本", "answers": [ "本名", "ほんみょう", "ほんめい" ], "comment": "本名 (ほんみょう, ほんめい): real name, real name"},
 { "question": "花本命進芸", "answers": [ "本命", "ほんめい" ], "comment": "本命 (ほんめい): favorite, favourite, sure thing, likely winner, certainty, one's heart's desire"},
 { "question": "本流徒進牛", "answers": [ "本流", "ほんりゅう" ], "comment": "本流 (ほんりゅう): main current, main current of thought"},
 { "question": "術名作事明", "answers": [ "名作", "めいさく" ], "comment": "名作 (めいさく): masterpiece"},
 { "question": "世場実名女", "answers": [ "実名", "じつめい", "名実", "めいじつ" ], "comment": "実名 (じつめい): real name\n名実 (めいじつ): in name and in reality, nominally and virtually, form and contents"},
 { "question": "進手雨名身", "answers": [ "名手", "めいしゅ" ], "comment": "名手 (めいしゅ): master, expert, expert board game player (chess, go, shogi, etc.)"},
 { "question": "面所夜春名", "answers": [ "名所", "めいしょ", "などころ" ], "comment": "名所 (めいしょ, などころ): famous place, name of a part (of an instrument, etc.), name and address, famous place, name of a part (of an instrument, etc.), name and address"},
 { "question": "安重春名人", "answers": [ "人名", "じんめい", "名人", "めいじん" ], "comment": "人名 (じんめい): person's name\n名人 (めいじん): master, expert"},
 { "question": "名声気草園", "answers": [ "名声", "めいせい" ], "comment": "名声 (めいせい): fame, reputation, renown"},
 { "question": "前体名楽会", "answers": [ "前名", "ぜんめい", "名前", "なまえ" ], "comment": "前名 (ぜんめい): one's previous name\n名前 (なまえ): name, full name, given name, first name"},
 { "question": "物名術足給", "answers": [ "名物", "めいぶつ" ], "comment": "名物 (めいぶつ): famous product, special product, speciality, specialty"},
 { "question": "名日目写火", "answers": [ "名目", "めいもく", "みょうもく" ], "comment": "名目 (めいもく, みょうもく): name, title, appellation, (something) nominal, (under the) pretext (of), pretense, name, title, appellation, (something) nominal, (under the) pretext (of), pretense"},
 { "question": "所中力発命", "answers": [ "命中", "めいちゅう" ], "comment": "命中 (めいちゅう): a hit, hitting something that was aimed at"},
 { "question": "命配徒日力", "answers": [ "命日", "めいにち" ], "comment": "命日 (めいにち): death anniversary"},
 { "question": "名牛命明集", "answers": [ "命名", "めいめい" ], "comment": "命名 (めいめい): naming, christening"},
 { "question": "力場記明給", "answers": [ "明記", "めいき" ], "comment": "明記 (めいき): clear writing, specification"},
 { "question": "言明数風道", "answers": [ "言明", "げんめい", "明言", "めいげん" ], "comment": "言明 (げんめい): declaration, statement, assertion\n明言 (めいげん): declaration, statement"},
 { "question": "面命新火会", "answers": [ "面会", "めんかい" ], "comment": "面会 (めんかい): meeting (face-to-face), interview"},
 { "question": "年格力白面", "answers": [ "面白", "おもしろ", "白面", "はくめん", "しらふ" ], "comment": "面白 (おもしろ): amusing, interesting\n白面 (はくめん, しらふ): fair complexion, face without makeup, inexperience, sobriety, soberness, sober face"},
 { "question": "行世面目男", "answers": [ "面目", "めんぼく", "めんもく", "めいぼく", "目面", "めづら", "めつら" ], "comment": "面目 (めんぼく, めんもく, めいぼく): face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look, face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look, face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look\n目面 (めづら, めつら): face and eyes, look, expression, features, face and eyes, look, expression, features"},
 { "question": "安日目新会", "answers": [ "目安", "めやす", "安目", "やすめ" ], "comment": "目安 (めやす): criterion, standard, yardstick, reference, aim, rough estimate, approximation\n安目 (やすめ): on the cheap side, comparatively cheap"},
 { "question": "意先交目徒", "answers": [ "目先", "めさき" ], "comment": "目先 (めさき): near future, immediate, before one's eyes, under one's nose"},
 { "question": "交目前学意", "answers": [ "目前", "もくぜん" ], "comment": "目前 (もくぜん): before one's very eyes, under one's nose, imminence, close at hand"},
 { "question": "音白目男世", "answers": [ "目白", "めじろ", "メジロ", "白目", "しろめ", "しろめ" ], "comment": "目白 (めじろ, メジロ): white-eye family of birds (Zosteropidae), Japanese white-eye (Zosterops japonicus), white-eye family of birds (Zosteropidae), Japanese white-eye (Zosterops japonicus)\n白目 (しろめ, しろめ): white of the eye, cold, unwelcoming eyes, white of the eye, cold, unwelcoming eyes, pewter, solder, pewter, solder, pewter, solder, pewter, solder"},
 { "question": "草合足学夜", "answers": [ "夜学", "やがく" ], "comment": "夜学 (やがく): evening course, night-school"},
 { "question": "念間格夜足", "answers": [ "夜間", "やかん" ], "comment": "夜間 (やかん): at night, nighttime"},
 { "question": "夜国作空火", "answers": [ "夜空", "よぞら" ], "comment": "夜空 (よぞら): night sky"},
 { "question": "声合夜中代", "answers": [ "夜中", "よなか", "やちゅう", "よじゅう", "中夜", "ちゅうや" ], "comment": "夜中 (よなか, やちゅう, よじゅう): midnight, dead of night, during the night, at night, all night, the whole night\n中夜 (ちゅうや): midnight period, midnight service, winter solstice"},
 { "question": "用場意花学", "answers": [ "用意", "ようい" ], "comment": "用意 (ようい): preparation, arrangements, provision, getting ready, laying out (e.g. a meal)"},
 { "question": "物写紙用世", "answers": [ "用紙", "ようし" ], "comment": "用紙 (ようし): blank form, sheets of paper, sheet of paper"},
 { "question": "給間用歩事", "answers": [ "用事", "ようじ" ], "comment": "用事 (ようじ): tasks, things to do, errand, business (to take care of), affairs, engagement"},
 { "question": "用歩心長新", "answers": [ "用心", "ようじん" ], "comment": "用心 (ようじん): care, precaution, guarding, caution"},
 { "question": "科用水園年", "answers": [ "用水", "ようすい" ], "comment": "用水 (ようすい): irrigation water, water for fire, city water, cistern water"},
 { "question": "地徒給用王", "answers": [ "用地", "ようち" ], "comment": "用地 (ようち): site"},
 { "question": "科月徒理身", "answers": [ "理科", "りか" ], "comment": "理科 (りか): science"},
 { "question": "学理元器車", "answers": [ "学理", "がくり", "理学", "りがく" ], "comment": "学理 (がくり): scholarly principle, scientific principle\n理学 (りがく): physical science (e.g. chemistry, biology, etc.), physics, lixue (Song-era Chinese philosophy), philosophy"},
 { "question": "理交立声事", "answers": [ "事理", "じり", "理事", "りじ" ], "comment": "事理 (じり): reason, facts, propriety, sense\n理事 (りじ): director, board of directors"},
 { "question": "念歩前分理", "answers": [ "理念", "りねん" ], "comment": "理念 (りねん): (Platonic) ideal (of how things ought to be, e.g. human rights), foundational principle, idea, conception (e.g. of the university), doctrine, ideology"},
 { "question": "立楽術念場", "answers": [ "立場", "たちば" ], "comment": "立場 (たちば): standpoint, position, situation"},
 { "question": "世体立心進", "answers": [ "立体", "りったい" ], "comment": "立体 (りったい): solid body, three-dimensional object, multi-storey car park"},
 { "question": "出強園新流", "answers": [ "流出", "りゅうしゅつ" ], "comment": "流出 (りゅうしゅつ): discharge, outward flow, efflux, effluence, haemorrhage, hemorrhage, bleeding (e.g. ink into paper), leak of (private) information or pictures"},
 { "question": "面肉歩入流", "answers": [ "流入", "りゅうにゅう" ], "comment": "流入 (りゅうにゅう): afflux, influx"},
 { "question": "白歩用学流", "answers": [ "流用", "りゅうよう" ], "comment": "流用 (りゅうよう): diversion, appropriation (e.g. of funds), misappropriation, re-use (e.g. old computer parts), recycling"},
 { "question": "学言楽色力", "answers": [ "学力", "がくりょく", "力学", "りきがく" ], "comment": "学力 (がくりょく): scholarly ability, scholarship, knowledge, literary ability\n力学 (りきがく): mechanics, dynamics"},
 { "question": "世作言力肉", "answers": [ "力作", "りきさく" ], "comment": "力作 (りきさく): tour de force, painstaking piece of work, achievement"},
 { "question": "牛身念和交", "answers": [ "和牛", "わぎゅう" ], "comment": "和牛 (わぎゅう): Wagyu beef, Japanese beef"},
 { "question": "流歩和紙事", "answers": [ "和紙", "わし" ], "comment": "和紙 (わし): washi, Japanese paper"},
 { "question": "食和科交雨", "answers": [ "和食", "わしょく" ], "comment": "和食 (わしょく): Japanese food, Japanese-style meal, Japanese cuisine"},
 { "question": "和言理風肉", "answers": [ "和風", "わふう" ], "comment": "和風 (わふう): Japanese style, light wind, moderate breeze"},
 { "question": "見雨園水身", "answers": [ "雨水", "あまみず", "うすい" ], "comment": "雨水 (あまみず, うすい): rain water, \"rain water\" solar term (approx. Feb 19), rain water, \"rain water\" solar term (approx. Feb 19)"},
 { "question": "色立集車音", "answers": [ "音色", "ねいろ", "おんしょく" ], "comment": "音色 (ねいろ, おんしょく): tone color, tone colour, tone quality, timbre, synthesizer patch, synthesiser patch, tone color, tone colour, tone quality, timbre, synthesizer patch, synthesiser patch"},
 { "question": "園花体強元", "answers": [ "花園", "はなぞの", "かえん" ], "comment": "花園 (はなぞの, かえん): flower garden, flower garden"},
 { "question": "器集国出日", "answers": [ "日出国", "ひいずるくに", "ひいづるくに", "にっしゅつこく" ], "comment": "日出国 (ひいずるくに, ひいづるくに, にっしゅつこく): Land of the Rising Sun, Land of the Rising Sun, Land of the Rising Sun"},
 { "question": "本雨理出所", "answers": [ "出所", "しゅっしょ", "でどころ", "でどこ", "所出", "しょしゅつ" ], "comment": "出所 (しゅっしょ, でどころ, でどこ): origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action, origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action, origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action\n所出 (しょしゅつ): one's birthplace, source"},
 { "question": "強声出生見", "answers": [ "出生", "しゅっしょう", "しゅっせい" ], "comment": "出生 (しゅっしょう, しゅっせい): birth, birth"},
 { "question": "心人草入器", "answers": [ "人心", "じんしん", "ひとごころ" ], "comment": "人心 (じんしん, ひとごころ): human nature, human heart, human spirit, kindness, sympathy, human nature, human heart, human spirit, kindness, sympathy"},
 { "question": "雨数言人元", "answers": [ "数人", "すうにん", "人数", "にんずう", "ひとかず", "にんず" ], "comment": "数人 (すうにん): several people\n人数 (にんずう, ひとかず, にんず): the number of people, many people, a large number of people, the number of people, many people, a large number of people, the number of people, many people, a large number of people"},
 { "question": "所人半文交", "answers": [ "人文", "じんぶん", "じんもん", "文人", "ぶんじん", "ふみびと" ], "comment": "人文 (じんぶん, じんもん): humanity, civilization, civilisation, culture, humanity, civilization, civilisation, culture\n文人 (ぶんじん, ふみびと): person of letters, literary person, person of letters, poet"},
 { "question": "目人言花親", "answers": [ "人目", "ひとめ", "じんもく" ], "comment": "人目 (ひとめ, じんもく): public gaze, public notice, public gaze, public notice"},
 { "question": "半肉徒入前", "answers": [ "前半", "ぜんはん", "ぜんぱん" ], "comment": "前半 (ぜんはん, ぜんぱん): first half, first half"},
 { "question": "進牛国外内", "answers": [ "国内外", "こくないがい" ], "comment": "国内外 (こくないがい): domestic and foreign, inside and outside the country"},
 { "question": "数意雨流日", "answers": [ "数日", "すうじつ", "日数", "にっすう", "ひかず" ], "comment": "数日 (すうじつ): few days\n日数 (にっすう, ひかず): a number of days, a number of days"},
 { "question": "王面本園日", "answers": [ "本日", "ほんじつ", "日本", "にほん", "にっぽん" ], "comment": "本日 (ほんじつ): today\n日本 (にほん, にっぽん): Japan, Japan"},
 { "question": "心年所月歩", "answers": [ "年月", "としつき", "ねんげつ" ], "comment": "年月 (としつき, ねんげつ): months and years, months and years"},
 { "question": "親強足発時", "answers": [ "発足", "ほっそく", "はっそく" ], "comment": "発足 (ほっそく, はっそく): starting, inauguration, launch, founding, establishment, start-up, starting, inauguration, launch, founding, establishment, start-up"},
 { "question": "月半合器心", "answers": [ "半月", "はんつき", "はんげつ" ], "comment": "半月 (はんつき, はんげつ): half-moon, half month, semicircle, half-moon, half month, semicircle"},
 { "question": "理日牛立半", "answers": [ "半日", "はんにち", "はんじつ" ], "comment": "半日 (はんにち, はんじつ): half day, half day"},
 { "question": "術年言半色", "answers": [ "半年", "はんとし", "はんねん" ], "comment": "半年 (はんとし, はんねん): half year, half year"},
 { "question": "文本発女記", "answers": [ "本文", "ほんぶん", "ほんもん" ], "comment": "本文 (ほんぶん, ほんもん): text (of document), body (of letter), text (of document), body (of letter)"},
 { "question": "明後日合立", "answers": [ "明後日", "あさって", "みょうごにち" ], "comment": "明後日 (あさって, みょうごにち): day after tomorrow, day after tomorrow"},
 { "question": "日合明園徒", "answers": [ "明日", "あした", "あす", "みょうにち" ], "comment": "明日 (あした, あす, みょうにち): tomorrow, near future, tomorrow, near future, tomorrow, near future"},
 { "question": "行流念真芸", "answers": [ "流行", "はやり", "りゅうこう" ], "comment": "流行 (はやり, りゅうこう): fashion, fad, vogue, craze, prevalence (e.g. of a disease), fashion, fad, vogue, craze, prevalence (e.g. of a disease)"},
 { "question": "時草和大念", "answers": [ "大和", "やまと" ], "comment": "大和 (やまと): Yamato, ancient province corresponding to modern-day Nara Prefecture, (ancient) Japan, Japanese"},
 { "question": "春足王世元", "answers": [ "足元", "あしもと" ], "comment": "足元 (あしもと): at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in \"watch your step\"), gait, pace, step, most recent, current, you, thou, at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in \"watch your step\"), gait, pace, step, most recent, current, you, thou"},
 { "question": "花歩立男生", "answers": [ "生花", "いけばな", "せいか" ], "comment": "生花 (いけばな, せいか): flower arrangement, fresh flowers, flower arrangement, fresh flowers"},
 { "question": "国科紙目術", "answers": [ "科目", "かもく" ], "comment": "科目 (かもく): (school) subject, curriculum, course"},
 { "question": "事気明身合", "answers": [ "気合", "きあい" ], "comment": "気合 (きあい): scream, yell, fighting spirit"},
 { "question": "立代交所音", "answers": [ "交代", "こうたい" ], "comment": "交代 (こうたい): alternation, change, relief, relay, shift, substitution (sports, etc.), taking turns"},
 { "question": "重後強体会", "answers": [ "体重", "たいじゅう", "重体", "じゅうたい" ], "comment": "体重 (たいじゅう): body weight, one's weight\n重体 (じゅうたい): seriously ill, serious condition, critical state"},
 { "question": "時身科所中", "answers": [ "中身", "なかみ", "身中", "しんちゅう" ], "comment": "中身 (なかみ): contents, interior, substance, filling, (sword) blade\n身中 (しんちゅう): within one's body"},
 { "question": "月日場実王", "answers": [ "月日", "つきひ", "がっぴ", "日月", "じつげつ", "にちげつ" ], "comment": "月日 (つきひ, がっぴ): time, years, days, (the) date\n日月 (じつげつ, にちげつ): sun and moon, time, days, years, sun and moon, time, days, years"},
 { "question": "男新芸国力", "answers": [ "国力", "こくりょく" ], "comment": "国力 (こくりょく): national power"},
 { "question": "心中交格歩", "answers": [ "心中", "しんじゅう", "しんぢゅう", "中心", "ちゅうしん", "心中", "しんちゅう", "中心", "なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes"},
 { "question": "草食半見集", "answers": [ "草食", "そうしょく", "食草", "しょくそう" ], "comment": "草食 (そうしょく): herbivorous, plant-eating, graminivorous\n食草 (しょくそう): edible grass (for insects), larval food plant"},
 { "question": "出大見長記", "answers": [ "長大", "ちょうだい" ], "comment": "長大 (ちょうだい): very long, great length"},
 { "question": "理作日給花", "answers": [ "日給", "にっきゅう" ], "comment": "日給 (にっきゅう): daily wages"},
 { "question": "世火道草身", "answers": [ "道草", "みちくさ" ], "comment": "道草 (みちくさ): loitering on the way, wayside grass"},
 { "question": "身音見所夜", "answers": [ "所見", "しょけん", "見所", "みどころ", "けんじょ", "けんしょ" ], "comment": "所見 (しょけん): view, opinion, finding, findings\n見所 (みどころ, けんじょ, けんしょ): point worthy of note, highlight (e.g. in a film), thing to note, good prospects for the future, promise, audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh), audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh)"},
 { "question": "年明立風後", "answers": [ "明後年", "みょうごねん" ], "comment": "明後年 (みょうごねん): year after next"},
 { "question": "草月名理牛", "answers": [ "名月", "めいげつ" ], "comment": "名月 (めいげつ): harvest moon, bright moon, full moon"},
 { "question": "園水後内強", "answers": [ "園内", "えんない" ], "comment": "園内 (えんない): inside the garden (park)"},
 { "question": "言間牛歩配", "answers": [ "牛歩", "ぎゅうほ" ], "comment": "牛歩 (ぎゅうほ): snail's pace, slow progress"},
 { "question": "術会立後間", "answers": [ "術後", "じゅつご" ], "comment": "術後 (じゅつご): postoperative"},
 { "question": "合身水器長", "answers": [ "身長", "しんちょう", "長身", "ちょうしん" ], "comment": "身長 (しんちょう): height (of body), stature\n長身 (ちょうしん): tall figure, high stature"},
 { "question": "外配本徒進", "answers": [ "配本", "はいほん" ], "comment": "配本 (はいほん): distribution of books"},
 { "question": "念世色白器", "answers": [ "色白", "いろじろ", "白色", "はくしょく" ], "comment": "色白 (いろじろ): fair-skinned, light-complexioned\n白色 (はくしょく): white"},
 { "question": "長芸力安用", "answers": [ "安芸", "あき" ], "comment": "安芸 (あき): former name of Hiroshima prefecture"},
 { "question": "内物立流紙", "answers": [ "物流", "ぶつりゅう" ], "comment": "物流 (ぶつりゅう): (physical) distribution, distribution of goods, logistics"},
 { "question": "交内月重白", "answers": [ "月内", "げつない" ], "comment": "月内 (げつない): by the end of this month"},
 { "question": "理後白内進", "answers": [ "後進", "こうしん" ], "comment": "後進 (こうしん): one's junior, next generation, reversing, going astern, going backwards"},
 { "question": "行楽真地科", "answers": [ "行楽地", "こうらくち" ], "comment": "行楽地 (こうらくち): tourist resort, holiday resort"},
 { "question": "事牛時命声", "answers": [ "時事", "じじ" ], "comment": "時事 (じじ): events of the day, current affairs"},
 { "question": "時地親芸力", "answers": [ "地力", "ちりょく", "じりき" ], "comment": "地力 (ちりょく, じりき): fertility, one's own potential, real ability, one's own strength"},
 { "question": "年時流道真", "answers": [ "時流", "じりゅう" ], "comment": "時流 (じりゅう): fashion (current) of the times, general drift of affairs"},
 { "question": "新事番春器", "answers": [ "新春", "しんしゅん" ], "comment": "新春 (しんしゅん): New Year (Spring)"},
 { "question": "時体記国集", "answers": [ "国体", "こくたい" ], "comment": "国体 (こくたい): national polity, National Athletic Meet"},
 { "question": "国肉術声記", "answers": [ "肉声", "にくせい" ], "comment": "肉声 (にくせい): natural voice (without a microphone)"},
 { "question": "音理配生学", "answers": [ "生理学", "せいりがく" ], "comment": "生理学 (せいりがく): physiology"},
 { "question": "国記目学物", "answers": [ "国学", "こくがく" ], "comment": "国学 (こくがく): study of (ancient) Japanese literature and culture, provincial school (under Japan's ritsuryo system and pre-Sui Chinese law)"},
 { "question": "国意写人言", "answers": [ "国人", "こくじん", "くにびと", "こくにん", "くにうど", "くにゅうど" ], "comment": "国人 (こくじん, くにびと, こくにん, くにうど, くにゅうど): indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period)"},
 { "question": "国文学火世", "answers": [ "国文学", "こくぶんがく" ], "comment": "国文学 (こくぶんがく): Japanese literature"},
 { "question": "時草和半真", "answers": [ "半時", "はんとき", "はんじ", "時半", "じはん" ], "comment": "半時 (はんとき, はんじ): little while, short time, an hour, half-hour, half an hour, little while, short time, an hour, half-hour, half an hour\n時半 (じはん): about an hour, short time, half past (the hour)"},
 { "question": "真足集写紙", "answers": [ "写真集", "しゃしんしゅう" ], "comment": "写真集 (しゃしんしゅう): collection of photographs, photoalbum"},
 { "question": "用声車本中", "answers": [ "車中", "しゃちゅう" ], "comment": "車中 (しゃちゅう): in a train or vehicle"},
 { "question": "出手中面器", "answers": [ "中手", "なかて", "手中", "しゅちゅう" ], "comment": "中手 (なかて): mid-season crops, mid-season rice, mid-season vegetables, metacarpus\n手中 (しゅちゅう): in one's hands, in one's control"},
 { "question": "所交発給物", "answers": [ "発給", "はっきゅう" ], "comment": "発給 (はっきゅう): issuance (e.g. of a passport), issuing"},
 { "question": "所春目体場", "answers": [ "春場所", "はるばしょ" ], "comment": "春場所 (はるばしょ): spring (March) tournament, held in Osaka"},
 { "question": "意進新足肉", "answers": [ "新進", "しんしん" ], "comment": "新進 (しんしん): rising, up-and-coming"},
 { "question": "重色記親交", "answers": [ "親交", "しんこう" ], "comment": "親交 (しんこう): intimacy, friendship, friendly relations"},
 { "question": "発手番真半", "answers": [ "番手", "ばんて", "手番", "てつがい" ], "comment": "番手 (ばんて): (yarn) count, n-th place (e.g. in a race), n-th in position (e.g. a starting lineup)\n手番 (てつがい): plan, arrangements"},
 { "question": "記科地言中", "answers": [ "地中", "ちちゅう" ], "comment": "地中 (ちちゅう): underground, subterranean"},
 { "question": "外文歩場男", "answers": [ "外場", "がいば", "場外", "じょうがい" ], "comment": "外場 (がいば): external field\n場外 (じょうがい): outside the hall (or stadium, market, etc.), off the grounds, off the premises, off-track"},
 { "question": "大徒配時代", "answers": [ "大時代", "おおじだい", "だいじだい" ], "comment": "大時代 (おおじだい, だいじだい): old-fashioned, antiquated, anachronistic, old-fashioned, antiquated, anachronistic"},
 { "question": "番道大給集", "answers": [ "大道", "だいどう", "たいどう" ], "comment": "大道 (だいどう, たいどう): main street, avenue, main street, avenue"},
 { "question": "名日意気心", "answers": [ "心意気", "こころいき" ], "comment": "心意気 (こころいき): spirit, disposition"},
 { "question": "長雨事親真", "answers": [ "長雨", "ながあめ", "ながめ" ], "comment": "長雨 (ながあめ, ながめ): long spell of rain, long spell of rain"},
 { "question": "歩命生器力", "answers": [ "生命力", "せいめいりょく" ], "comment": "生命力 (せいめいりょく): vitality, (one's) life force"},
 { "question": "地時女立科", "answers": [ "立地", "りっち" ], "comment": "立地 (りっち): site, location (e.g. of industry)"},
 { "question": "写新立用国", "answers": [ "国立", "こくりつ", "立国", "りっこく" ], "comment": "国立 (こくりつ): national\n立国 (りっこく): founding of a nation"},
 { "question": "写白交地命", "answers": [ "白地", "あからさま", "しろじ", "しらじ", "はくち" ], "comment": "白地 (あからさま, しろじ, しらじ, はくち): plain, frank, candid, open, direct, straightforward, unabashed, blatant, flagrant, white background, blank, female virgin, white background, blank, female virgin, white cloth, empty land, empty lot, amateur (of a prostitute, etc)"},
 { "question": "日芸出集内", "answers": [ "日出", "にっしゅつ" ], "comment": "日出 (にっしゅつ): sunrise"},
 { "question": "数間後配時", "answers": [ "数時間", "すうじかん" ], "comment": "数時間 (すうじかん): a few hours"},
 { "question": "間分意目術", "answers": [ "分間", "ふんかん" ], "comment": "分間 (ふんかん): minutes (period of)"},
 { "question": "入体身集王", "answers": [ "身体", "からだ", "しんたい", "しんだい", "しんてい" ], "comment": "身体 (からだ, しんたい, しんだい, しんてい): body, torso, trunk, build, physique, constitution, health, corpse, dead body, body, physical system, person, body, physical system, person, body, physical system, person"}
]
}
